<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Install Docker Engine on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Install Docker Engine on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine from binaries</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/binaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/binaries/</guid>
      <description>Important&#xA;This page contains information on how to install Docker using binaries. These instructions are mostly suitable for testing purposes. We do not recommend installing Docker using binaries in production environments as they don&#39;t have automatic security updates. The Linux binaries described on this page are statically linked, which means that vulnerabilities in build-time dependencies are not automatically patched by security updates of your Linux distribution.&#xA;Updating binaries is also slightly more involved when compared to Docker packages installed using a package manager or through Docker Desktop, as it requires (manually) updating the installed version whenever there is a new release of Docker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine on CentOS</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/centos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/centos/</guid>
      <description>To get started with Docker Engine on CentOS, make sure you meet the prerequisites, and then follow the installation steps.&#xA;Prerequisites OS requirements To install Docker Engine, you need a maintained version of one of the following CentOS versions:&#xA;CentOS 9 (stream) The centos-extras repository must be enabled. This repository is enabled by default. If you have disabled it, you need to re-enable it.&#xA;Uninstall old versions Older versions of Docker went by docker or docker-engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine on Debian</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/debian/</guid>
      <description>To get started with Docker Engine on Debian, make sure you meet the prerequisites, and then follow the installation steps.&#xA;Prerequisites Firewall limitations Warning&#xA;Before you install Docker, make sure you consider the following security implications and firewall incompatibilities.&#xA;If you use ufw or firewalld to manage firewall settings, be aware that when you expose container ports using Docker, these ports bypass your firewall rules. For more information, refer to Docker and ufw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine on Fedora</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/fedora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/fedora/</guid>
      <description>To get started with Docker Engine on Fedora, make sure you meet the prerequisites, and then follow the installation steps.&#xA;Prerequisites OS requirements To install Docker Engine, you need a maintained version of one of the following Fedora versions:&#xA;Fedora 39 Fedora 40 Uninstall old versions Older versions of Docker went by docker or docker-engine. Uninstall any such older versions before attempting to install a new version, along with associated dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine on Raspberry Pi OS (32-bit)</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/raspberry-pi-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/raspberry-pi-os/</guid>
      <description>To get started with Docker Engine on Raspberry Pi OS, make sure you meet the prerequisites, and then follow the installation steps.&#xA;Important&#xA;This installation instruction refers to the 32-bit (armhf) version of Raspberry Pi OS. If you&#39;re using the 64-bit (arm64) version, follow the instructions for Debian.&#xA;Prerequisites Firewall limitations Warning&#xA;Before you install Docker, make sure you consider the following security implications and firewall incompatibilities.&#xA;If you use ufw or firewalld to manage firewall settings, be aware that when you expose container ports using Docker, these ports bypass your firewall rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine on RHEL</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/rhel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/rhel/</guid>
      <description>Experimental&#xA;Support for Docker Engine on RHEL x86_64 and aarch64 is experimental.&#xA;Docker Desktop for Linux is also available for RHEL.&#xA;To get access, join the Early Access Program.&#xA;To get started with Docker Engine on RHEL, make sure you meet the prerequisites, and then follow the installation steps.&#xA;Prerequisites OS requirements To install Docker Engine, you need a maintained version of one of the following RHEL versions:&#xA;RHEL 8 RHEL 9 Uninstall old versions Older versions of Docker went by docker or docker-engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine on SLES (s390x)</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/sles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/sles/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;The installation instructions on this page refer to packages for SLES on the s390x architecture (IBM Z). Other architectures, including x86_64, aren&#39;t supported for SLES.&#xA;To get started with Docker Engine on SLES, make sure you meet the prerequisites, and then follow the installation steps.&#xA;Prerequisites OS requirements To install Docker Engine, you need a maintained version of one of the following SLES versions:&#xA;SLES 15-SP4 on s390x (IBM Z) SLES 15-SP5 on s390x (IBM Z) You must enable the SCC SUSE repositories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Engine on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>To get started with Docker Engine on Ubuntu, make sure you meet the prerequisites, and then follow the installation steps.&#xA;Prerequisites Firewall limitations Warning&#xA;Before you install Docker, make sure you consider the following security implications and firewall incompatibilities.&#xA;If you use ufw or firewalld to manage firewall settings, be aware that when you expose container ports using Docker, these ports bypass your firewall rules. For more information, refer to Docker and ufw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux post-installation steps for Docker Engine</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/linux-postinstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/linux-postinstall/</guid>
      <description>These optional post-installation procedures describe how to configure your Linux host machine to work better with Docker.&#xA;Manage Docker as a non-root user The Docker daemon binds to a Unix socket, not a TCP port. By default it&#39;s the root user that owns the Unix socket, and other users can only access it using sudo. The Docker daemon always runs as the root user.&#xA;If you don&#39;t want to preface the docker command with sudo, create a Unix group called docker and add users to it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
