<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker account overview on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/accounts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker account overview on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/accounts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deactivating a user account</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/accounts/deactivate-user-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/accounts/deactivate-user-account/</guid>
      <description>You can deactivate an account at any time. This section describes the prerequisites and steps to deactivate a user account. For information on deactivating an organization, see Deactivating an organization.&#xA;Warning&#xA;All Docker products and services that use your Docker account will be inaccessible after deactivating your account.&#xA;Prerequisites Before deactivating your Docker account, ensure that you meet the following requirements:&#xA;You must not be a member of a company or any teams or organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage your Docker account</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/accounts/manage-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/accounts/manage-account/</guid>
      <description>You can centrally manage the settings for your Docker account. Here you can also take administrative actions for your account and manage your account security.&#xA;Tip&#xA;If your account is associated with an organization that enforces single sign-on (SSO), you may not have permissions to update your account settings. You need to contact your administrator to update your settings.&#xA;Update general settings Sign in to your Docker account. In Docker Home, select your avatar in the top-right corner to open the drop-down.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
