<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview of Docker Hub on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview of Docker Hub on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/api/dvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/api/dvp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/api/latest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/api/latest/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hub API v1 (deprecated)</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/api/deprecated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/api/deprecated/</guid>
      <description>Deprecated&#xA;Docker Hub API v1 has been deprecated. Please use Docker Hub API v2 instead.&#xA;The following API routes within the v1 path will no longer work and will return a 410 status code:&#xA;/v1/repositories/{name}/images /v1/repositories/{name}/tags /v1/repositories/{name}/tags/{tag_name} /v1/repositories/{namespace}/{name}/images /v1/repositories/{namespace}/{name}/tags /v1/repositories/{namespace}/{name}/tags/{tag_name} If you want to continue using the Docker Hub API in your current applications, update your clients to use v2 endpoints.&#xA;OLD NEW /v1/repositories/{name}/images /v2/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images /v1/repositories/{namespace}/{name}/images /v2/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images /v1/repositories/{name}/tags /v2/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/tags /v1/repositories/{namespace}/{name}/tags /v2/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/tags /v1/repositories/{namespace}/{name}/tags /v2/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/tags/{tag} /v1/repositories/{namespace}/{name}/tags/{tag_name} /v2/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/tags/{tag} </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hub quickstart</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>The following section contains step-by-step instructions on how to get started with Docker Hub.&#xA;Step 1: Sign up for a free Docker account Start by creating a Docker ID.&#xA;A Docker ID grants you access to Docker Hub repositories and lets you explore available images from the community and verified publishers. You also need a Docker ID to share images on Docker Hub.&#xA;Tip&#xA;Explore Docker&#39;s core subscriptions to see what else Docker can offer you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hub rate limit</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/download-rate-limit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/download-rate-limit/</guid>
      <description>What&#39;s the download rate limit on Docker Hub? Docker Hub limits the number of Docker image downloads, or pulls, based on the account type of the user pulling the image. Pull rate limits are based on individual IP address.&#xA;User type Rate limit Anonymous users 100 pulls per 6 hours per IP address Authenticated users 200 pulls per 6 hour period Users with a paid Docker subscription Up to 5000 pulls per day If you require a higher number of pulls, you can also buy an Enhanced Service Account add-on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hub release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Here you can learn about the latest changes, new features, bug fixes, and known issues for each Docker Hub release.&#xA;Take a look at the Docker Public Roadmap to see what&#39;s coming next.&#xA;2024-03-23 New You can tag Docker Hub repositories with categories. 2023-12-11 The Advanced Image Management feature, along with the corresponding API endpoints, has been retired. See docker/roadmap#534.&#xA;The following API endpoints have been removed:&#xA;/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images /namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images/{digest}/tags /namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images-summary /namespaces/{namespace}/delete-images 2023-08-28 Organizations with SSO enabled can assign members to roles, organizations, and teams with SCIM role mapping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCI artifacts on Docker Hub</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/oci-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/oci-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>You can use Docker Hub to store any kind of software artifact, not just container images. Docker Hub supports OCI artifacts by leveraging the config property on the image manifest.&#xA;What are OCI artifacts? OCI artifacts are any arbitrary files related to a software application. Some examples include:&#xA;Helm charts Software Bill of Materials (SBOM) Digital signatures Provenance data Attestations Vulnerability reports Docker Hub supporting OCI artifacts means you can use one repository for storing and distributing container images as well as other assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registry as a pull through cache</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/mirror/</guid>
      <description>Use-case If you have multiple instances of Docker running in your environment, such as multiple physical or virtual machines all running Docker, each daemon goes out to the internet and fetches an image it doesn&#39;t have locally, from the Docker repository. You can run a local registry mirror and point all your daemons there, to avoid this extra internet traffic.&#xA;Note&#xA;Docker Official Images are an intellectual property of Docker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service accounts</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/service-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/service-accounts/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Service accounts require a Docker Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;A service account is a Docker ID used for automated management of container images or containerized applications. Service accounts are typically used in automated workflows, and don&#39;t share Docker IDs with the members in the organization. Common use cases for service accounts include mirroring content on Docker Hub, or tying in image pulls from your CI/CD process.&#xA;Note&#xA;All paid Docker subscriptions include up to 5000 pulls per day per authenticated user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Static vulnerability scanning</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/vulnerability-scanning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/vulnerability-scanning/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;This page describes the legacy static vulnerability scanning feature of Docker Hub. There&#39;s also Docker Scout, which provides more detailed and always up-to-date results, guided remediation steps for improving your security posture, and more.&#xA;Docker Hub static scanning requires a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;Docker Hub static vulnerability scanning lets you automatically run a point-in-time scan on your Docker images for vulnerabilities.&#xA;When you push an image to a Docker Hub repository after turning on static scanning, Docker Hub automatically scans the image to identify vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webhooks</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/webhooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/webhooks/</guid>
      <description>You can use webhooks to cause an action in another service in response to a push event in the repository. Webhooks are POST requests sent to a URL you define in Docker Hub.&#xA;Create a webhook To create a webhook:&#xA;In your chosen repository, select the Webhooks tab. Provide a name for the webhook. Provide a destination webhook URL. This is where webhook POST requests are delivered. Select Create. View webhook delivery history To view the history of the webhook:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
