<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deploy with Microsoft installer on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deploy with Microsoft installer on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install and configure</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/install-and-configure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/install-and-configure/</guid>
      <description>Install interactively In the Docker Admin Console, navigate to your organization.&#xA;Under Security and access, select the Deploy Docker Desktop page.&#xA;Select the Download MSI installer button.&#xA;Once downloaded, double-click Docker Desktop Installer.msi to run the installer.&#xA;Once you&#39;ve accepted the license agreement, you can choose the install location. By default, Docker Desktop is installed at C:\Program Files\Docker\Docker.&#xA;Configure the Docker Desktop installation. You can:&#xA;Create a desktop shortcut</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/faq/</guid>
      <description>What happens to user data if they have an older Docker Desktop installation (i.e. .exe)? If they have an older .exe installation, users must uninstall this version before using the new MSI version. This deletes all Docker containers, images, volumes, and other Docker-related data local to the machine, and removes the files generated by the application. For older versions, users should backup any containers that they want to keep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/use-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/use-intune/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Docker Desktop using Intune, Microsoft&#39;s cloud-based device management tool.&#xA;Sign in to your Intune admin center.&#xA;Add a new app. Select Apps, then Windows, then Add.&#xA;For the app type, select Windows app (Win32)&#xA;Select the intunewin package.&#xA;Complete any relevant details such as the description, publisher, or app version and then select Next.&#xA;Optional: On the Program tab, you can update the Install command field to suit your needs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
