<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview of Docker Extensions on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview of Docker Extensions on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Configure a private marketplace for extensions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/private-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/private-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Beta&#xA;This feature is currently in Beta. It is available to Docker Business customers only.&#xA;Learn how to configure and set up a private marketplace with a curated list of extensions for your Docker Desktop users.&#xA;It is designed specifically&#xA;Docker Extensions&#39; private marketplace is designed specifically for organizations who don’t give developers root access to their machines. It makes use of Settings Management so administrators have complete control over the private marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketplace extensions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>There are two types of extensions available in the Extensions Marketplace:&#xA;Docker-reviewed extensions Self-published extensions Docker-reviewed extensions are manually reviewed by the Docker Extensions team to ensure an extra level of trust and quality. They appear as Reviewed in the Marketplace.&#xA;Self-published extensions are autonomously published by extension developers and go through an automated validation process. They appear as Not reviewed in the Marketplace.&#xA;Install an extension Note&#xA;For some extensions, a separate account needs to be created before use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Marketplace extensions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/non-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/non-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Install an extension not available in the Marketplace Warning&#xA;Docker Extensions that are not in the Marketplace haven&#39;t gone through Docker&#39;s review process. Extensions can install binaries, invoke commands and access files on your machine. Installing them is at your own risk.&#xA;The Extensions Marketplace is the trusted and official place to install extensions from within Docker Desktop. These extensions have gone through a review process by Docker. However, other extensions can also be installed in Docker Desktop if you trust the extension author.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings and feedback for Docker Extensions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/settings-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions/settings-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Settings Turn on or turn off extensions Docker Extensions is switched on by default. To change your settings:&#xA;Navigate to Settings. Select the Extensions tab. Next to Enable Docker Extensions, select or clear the checkbox to set your desired state. In the bottom-right corner, select Apply &amp;amp; Restart. Note&#xA;If you are an organization owner, you can turn off extensions for your users. Open the settings.json file, and set &amp;quot;extensionsEnabled&amp;quot; to false.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
