<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Organization administration overview on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organization administration overview on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Activity logs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/activity-logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/activity-logs/</guid>
      <description>Activity logs display a chronological list of activities that occur at organization and repository levels. It provides a report to owners on all their member activities.&#xA;With activity logs, owners can view and track:&#xA;What changes were made The date when a change was made Who initiated the change For example, activity logs display activities such as the date when a repository was created or deleted, the member who created the repository, the name of the repository, and when there was a change to the privacy settings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and manage a team</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/manage-a-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/manage-a-team/</guid>
      <description>You can create teams for your organization in Docker Hub and the Docker Admin Console. You can configure repository access for a team in Docker Hub.&#xA;A team is a group of Docker users that belong to an organization. An organization can have multiple teams. An organization owner can then create new teams and add members to an existing team using their Docker ID or email address and by selecting a team the user should be part of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create your organization</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/orgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/orgs/</guid>
      <description>This section describes how to create an organization. Before you begin:&#xA;You need a Docker ID. Review the Docker subscriptions and features to determine what plan to choose for your organization. Create an organization There are multiple ways to create an organization. You can create a brand new organization using the Create Organization option in Docker Hub, or you can convert an existing user account to an organization. The following section contains instructions on how to create a new organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General organization settings</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/general-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/general-settings/</guid>
      <description>Early Access&#xA;The Docker Admin Console is an early access product.&#xA;It&#39;s available to all company owners and organization owners. You can still manage companies and organizations in Docker Hub, but the Admin Console includes enhanced features for company-level management.&#xA;This section describes how to manage organization settings in the Docker Admin Console.&#xA;Configure general information General organization information appears on your organization landing page in Docker Hub.&#xA;This information includes:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage organization members</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/members/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to manage members for your organization in Docker Hub and the Docker Admin Console.&#xA;Docker Hub Admin Console Invite members Owners can invite new members to an organization via Docker ID, email address, or via a CSV file containing email addresses. If an invitee does not have a Docker account, they must create an account and verify their email address before they can accept the invitation to join the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard your organization</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/onboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/organization/onboard/</guid>
      <description>Early Access&#xA;The Docker Admin Console is an early access product.&#xA;It&#39;s available to all company owners and organization owners. You can still manage companies and organizations in Docker Hub, but the Admin Console includes enhanced features for company-level management.&#xA;Learn how to onboard your organization using Docker Hub or the Docker Admin Console.&#xA;Onboarding your organization allows you to gain visibility into the activity of your users and enforce security settings.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
