<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Build drivers on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Build drivers on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker container build driver</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/docker-container/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/docker-container/</guid>
      <description>The Docker container driver allows creation of a managed and customizable BuildKit environment in a dedicated Docker container.&#xA;Using the Docker container driver has a couple of advantages over the default Docker driver. For example:&#xA;Specify custom BuildKit versions to use. Build multi-arch images, see QEMU Advanced options for cache import and export Synopsis Run the following command to create a new builder, named container, that uses the Docker container driver:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker driver</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/docker/</guid>
      <description>The Buildx Docker driver is the default driver. It uses the BuildKit server components built directly into the Docker engine. The Docker driver requires no configuration.&#xA;Unlike the other drivers, builders using the Docker driver can&#39;t be manually created. They&#39;re only created automatically from the Docker context.&#xA;Images built with the Docker driver are automatically loaded to the local image store.&#xA;Synopsis # The Docker driver is used by buildx by default docker buildx build .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes driver</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>The Kubernetes driver lets you connect your local development or CI environments to builders in a Kubernetes cluster to allow access to more powerful compute resources, optionally on multiple native architectures.&#xA;Synopsis Run the following command to create a new builder, named kube, that uses the Kubernetes driver:&#xA;$ docker buildx create \ --bootstrap \ --name=kube \ --driver=kubernetes \ --driver-opt=[key=value,...] The following table describes the available driver-specific options that you can pass to --driver-opt:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote driver</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/drivers/remote/</guid>
      <description>The Buildx remote driver allows for more complex custom build workloads, allowing you to connect to externally managed BuildKit instances. This is useful for scenarios that require manual management of the BuildKit daemon, or where a BuildKit daemon is exposed from another source.&#xA;Synopsis $ docker buildx create \ --name remote \ --driver remote \ tcp://localhost:1234 The following table describes the available driver-specific options that you can pass to --driver-opt:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
