<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Company overview on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Company overview on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create a company</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/new-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/new-company/</guid>
      <description>You can create a new company in Docker Hub or Docker Admin Console. Before you begin, make sure you&#39;re the owner of the organization you want to add to the new company. The organization also needs to have a Docker Business subscription.&#xA;Docker Hub Admin Console Create a company To create a new company:&#xA;In Docker Hub, navigate to the organization you want to place under a company. The organization must have a Business subscription, and you must be an owner of the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage company owners</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/owners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/owners/</guid>
      <description>As a company owner, you can configure Single Sign-on (SSO) and System for Cross-domain Identity Management (SCIM) for all organizations under the company.&#xA;Docker Hub Admin Console Add a company owner Sign in to Docker Hub, navigate to the Organizations page, and select your company. In the Overview tab, select Add owner and enter their Docker ID or email address. After you find the user, select Add company owner. Once you&#39;ve added the new owner, you can view the user in the Company owners table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage company users</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/users/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/users/</guid>
      <description>Early Access&#xA;The Docker Admin Console is an early access product.&#xA;It&#39;s available to all company owners and organization owners. You can still manage companies and organizations in Docker Hub, but the Admin Console includes enhanced features for company-level management.&#xA;You can manage users at the company-level in the Docker Admin Console.&#xA;Invite members Owners can invite new members to an organization via Docker ID, email address, or via a CSV file containing email addresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage organizations</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/company/organizations/</guid>
      <description>You can manage the organizations in a company in Docker Hub and the Docker Admin Console. In Docker Hub, you can manage seats and members at the organization-level. When you use the Admin Console, you can do more to manage organizations at the company-level.&#xA;Docker Hub Admin Console View all organizations In Docker Hub, select Organizations. Select your company. From the company page, you can view all organizations in the Overview tab.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
