<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker Official Images on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/official-images/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker Official Images on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/official-images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using Docker Official Images</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/official-images/using/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/official-images/using/</guid>
      <description>Docker recommends you use the Docker Official Images in your projects. These images have clear documentation, promote best practices, and are regularly updated. Docker Official Images support most common use cases, making them perfect for new Docker users. Advanced users can benefit from more specialized image variants as well as review Docker Official Images as part of your Dockerfile learning process.&#xA;Tags The repository description for each Docker Official Image contains a Supported tags and respective Dockerfile links section that lists all the current tags with links to the Dockerfiles that created the image with those tags.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to Docker Official Images</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/official-images/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/official-images/contributing/</guid>
      <description>Docker, Inc. sponsors a dedicated team that&#39;s responsible for reviewing and publishing all content in Docker Official Images. This team works in collaboration with upstream software maintainers, security experts, and the broader Docker community.&#xA;While it&#39;s preferable to have upstream software authors maintaining their Docker Official Images, this isn&#39;t a strict requirement. Creating and maintaining images for Docker Official Images is a collaborative process. It takes place openly on GitHub where participation is encouraged.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
