<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Generative AI guide on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/guides/use-case/genai-pdf-bot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Generative AI guide on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/guides/use-case/genai-pdf-bot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Containerize a generative AI application</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/guides/use-case/genai-pdf-bot/containerize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/guides/use-case/genai-pdf-bot/containerize/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Note&#xA;GenAI applications can often benefit from GPU acceleration. Currently Docker Desktop supports GPU acceleration only on Windows with the WSL2 backend. Linux users can also access GPU acceleration using a native installation of the Docker Engine.&#xA;You have installed the latest version of Docker Desktop or, if you are a Linux user and are planning to use GPU acceleration, Docker Engine. Docker adds new features regularly and some parts of this guide may work only with the latest version of Docker Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use containers for generative AI development</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/guides/use-case/genai-pdf-bot/develop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/guides/use-case/genai-pdf-bot/develop/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Complete Containerize a generative AI application.&#xA;Overview In this section, you&#39;ll learn how to set up a development environment to access all the services that your generative AI (GenAI) application needs. This includes:&#xA;Adding a local database Adding a local or remote LLM service Note&#xA;You can see more samples of containerized GenAI applications in the GenAI Stack demo applications.&#xA;Add a local database You can use containers to set up local services, like a database.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
