<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Use-case guides on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Use-case guides on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data science with JupyterLab</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>Docker and JupyterLab are two powerful tools that can enhance your data science workflow. In this guide, you will learn how to use them together to create and run reproducible data science environments. This guide is based on Supercharging AI/ML Development with JupyterLab and Docker.&#xA;In this guide, you&#39;ll learn how to:&#xA;Run a personal Jupyter Server with JupyterLab on your local machine Customize your JupyterLab environment Share your JupyterLab notebook and environment with other data scientists What is JupyterLab?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face detection with TensorFlow.js</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/tensorflowjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/tensorflowjs/</guid>
      <description>This guide introduces the seamless integration of TensorFlow.js with Docker to perform face detection. In this guide, you&#39;ll explore how to:&#xA;Run a containerized TensorFlow.js application using Docker. Implement face detection in a web application with TensorFlow.js. Construct a Dockerfile for a TensorFlow.js web application. Use Docker Compose for real-time application development and updates. Share your Docker image on Docker Hub to facilitate deployment and extend reach. Acknowledgment&#xA;Docker would like to thank Harsh Manvar for his contribution to this guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use containerized databases</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/databases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/use-case/databases/</guid>
      <description>Using a local containerized database offers flexibility and ease of setup, letting you mirror production environments closely without the overhead of traditional database installations. Docker simplifies this process, enabling you to deploy, manage, and scale databases in isolated containers with just a few commands.&#xA;In this guide, you&#39;ll learn how to:&#xA;Run a local containerized database Access the shell of a containerized database Connect to a containerized database from your host Connect to a containerized database from another container Persist database data in a volume Build a customized database image Use Docker Compose to run a database This guide uses the MySQL image for examples, but the concepts can be applied to other database images.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
