<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Explore Docker Desktop on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Explore Docker Desktop on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop&#39;s Resource Saver mode</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/resource-saver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/resource-saver/</guid>
      <description>Resource Saver is a new feature available in Docker Desktop version 4.24 and later. It significantly reduces Docker Desktop&#39;s CPU and memory utilization on the host by 2 GBs or more, by automatically stopping the Docker Desktop Linux VM when no containers are running for a period of time. The default time is set to 5 minutes, but this can be adjusted to suit your needs.&#xA;With Resource Saver mode, Docker Desktop uses minimal system resources when it&#39;s idle, thereby allowing you to save battery life on your laptop and improve your multi-tasking experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Builds</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/builds/</guid>
      <description>The Builds view is a simple interface that lets you inspect your build history and manage builders using Docker Desktop.&#xA;Opening the Builds view in Docker Desktop displays a list of completed builds. By default, the list is sorted by date, showing the most recent builds at the top. You can switch to Active builds to view any ongoing builds.&#xA;If you&#39;re connected to a cloud builder through Docker Build Cloud, the Builds view also lists any active or completed cloud builds by other team members connected to the same cloud builder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore the Containers view in Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/container/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/container/</guid>
      <description>The Containers view lists all your running containers and applications. You must have running or stopped containers and applications to see them listed.&#xA;Container actions Use the Search field to search for any specific container.&#xA;From the Containers view you can perform the following actions:&#xA;Pause/Resume Stop/Start/Restart View image packages and CVEs Delete Open the application in VS code Open the port exposed by the container in a browser Copy docker run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore the Images view in Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/images/</guid>
      <description>The Images view lets you manage Docker images without having to use the CLI. By default, it displays a list of all Docker images on your local disk.&#xA;You can also view Hub images once you have signed in to Docker Hub. This allows you to collaborate with your team and manage your images directly through Docker Desktop.&#xA;The Images view lets you perform core operations such as running an image as a container, pulling the latest version of an image from Docker Hub, pushing the image to Docker Hub, and inspecting images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Volumes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/volumes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/volumes/</guid>
      <description>The Volumes view in Docker Dashboard lets you create, delete, and perform other actions on your volumes. You can also see which volumes are being used as well as inspect the files and folders in your volumes.&#xA;View your volumes You can view the following information about your volumes:&#xA;Name: The name of the volume. Status: Whether the volume is in-use by a container or not. Created: How long ago the volume was created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pause Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/use-desktop/pause/</guid>
      <description>When Docker Desktop is paused, the Linux VM running Docker Engine is paused, the current state of all your containers are saved in memory, and all processes are frozen. This reduces the CPU and memory usage and helps you retain a longer battery life on your laptop.&#xA;You can manually pause Docker Desktop by selecting the Docker menu and then Pause. To manually resume Docker Desktop, select the Resume option in the Docker menu, or run any Docker CLI command.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
