<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Exporters overview on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Exporters overview on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Image and registry exporters</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/image-registry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/image-registry/</guid>
      <description>The image exporter outputs the build result into a container image format. The registry exporter is identical, but it automatically pushes the result by setting push=true.&#xA;Synopsis Build a container image using the image and registry exporters:&#xA;$ docker buildx build --output type=image[,parameters] . $ docker buildx build --output type=registry[,parameters] . The following table describes the available parameters that you can pass to --output for type=image:&#xA;Parameter Type Default Description name String Specify image name(s) push true,false false Push after creating the image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local and tar exporters</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/local-tar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/local-tar/</guid>
      <description>The local and tar exporters output the root filesystem of the build result into a local directory. They&#39;re useful for producing artifacts that aren&#39;t container images.&#xA;local exports files and directories. tar exports the same, but bundles the export into a tarball. Synopsis Build a container image using the local exporter:&#xA;$ docker buildx build --output type=local[,parameters] . $ docker buildx build --output type=tar[,parameters] . The following table describes the available parameters:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCI and Docker exporters</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/oci-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/exporters/oci-docker/</guid>
      <description>The oci exporter outputs the build result into an OCI image layout tarball. The docker exporter behaves the same way, except it exports a Docker image layout instead.&#xA;The docker driver doesn&#39;t support these exporters. You must use docker-container or some other driver if you want to generate these outputs.&#xA;Synopsis Build a container image using the oci and docker exporters:&#xA;$ docker buildx build --output type=oci[,parameters] . $ docker buildx build --output type=docker[,parameters] .</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
