<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integrating Docker Scout with environments on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/integrations/environment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Integrating Docker Scout with environments on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/scout/integrations/environment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Generic environment integration with CLI</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/integrations/environment/cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/scout/integrations/environment/cli/</guid>
      <description>You can create a generic environment integration by running the Docker Scout CLI client in your CI workflows. The CLI client is available as a binary on GitHub and as a container image on Docker Hub. Use the client to invoke the docker scout environment command to assign your images to environments.&#xA;For more information about how to use the docker scout environment command, refer to the CLI reference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Docker Scout with Sysdig</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/integrations/environment/sysdig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/scout/integrations/environment/sysdig/</guid>
      <description>The Sysdig integration enables Docker Scout to automatically detect the images you&#39;re using for your running workloads. Activating this integration gives you real-time insights about your security posture, and lets you compare your builds with what&#39;s running in production.&#xA;How it works The Sysdig Agent captures the images of your container workloads. Docker Scout integrates with the Sysdig API to discover the images in your cluster. This integration uses Sysdig&#39;s Risk Spotlight feature.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
