<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python language-specific guide on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python language-specific guide on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/language/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Configure CI/CD for your Python application</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/configure-ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/configure-ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Complete all the previous sections of this guide, starting with Containerize a Python application. You must have a GitHub account and a Docker account to complete this section.&#xA;Overview In this section, you&#39;ll learn how to set up and use GitHub Actions to build and test your Docker image as well as push it to Docker Hub. You will complete the following steps:&#xA;Create a new repository on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Containerize a Python application</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/containerize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/containerize/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites You have installed the latest version of Docker Desktop. You have a git client. The examples in this section use a command-line based git client, but you can use any client. Overview This section walks you through containerizing and running a Python application.&#xA;Get the sample application The sample application uses the popular Flask framework.&#xA;Clone the sample application to use with this guide. Open a terminal, change directory to a directory that you want to work in, and run the following command to clone the repository:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test your Python deployment</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/deploy/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Complete all the previous sections of this guide, starting with Containerize a Python application. Turn on Kubernetes in Docker Desktop. Overview In this section, you&#39;ll learn how to use Docker Desktop to deploy your application to a fully-featured Kubernetes environment on your development machine. This allows you to test and debug your workloads on Kubernetes locally before deploying.&#xA;Create a Kubernetes YAML file In your python-docker-dev directory, create a file named docker-python-kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use containers for Python development</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/develop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/language/python/develop/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Complete Containerize a Python application.&#xA;Overview In this section, you&#39;ll learn how to set up a development environment for your containerized application. This includes:&#xA;Adding a local database and persisting data Configuring Compose to automatically update your running Compose services as you edit and save your code Get the sample application You&#39;ll need to clone a new repository to get a sample application that includes logic to connect to the database.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
