<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Extension release process on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Extension release process on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build the extensions for multiple architectures</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/multi-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/multi-arch/</guid>
      <description>It is highly recommended that, at a minimum, your extension is supported for the following architectures:&#xA;linux/amd64 linux/arm64 Docker Desktop retrieves the extension image according to the user’s system architecture. If the extension does not provide an image that matches the user’s system architecture, Docker Desktop is not able to install the extension. As a result, users can’t run the extension in Docker Desktop.&#xA;Build and push for multiple architectures If you created an extension from the docker extension init command, the Makefile at the root of the directory includes a target with name push-extension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extension image labels</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/labels/</guid>
      <description>Extensions use image labels to provide additional information such as a title, description, screenshots, and more.&#xA;This information is then displayed as an overview of the extension, so users can choose to install it.&#xA;You can define image labels in the extension&#39;s Dockerfile.&#xA;Important&#xA;If any of the required labels are missing in the Dockerfile, Docker Desktop considers the extension invalid and doesn&#39;t list it in the Marketplace.&#xA;Here is the list of labels you can or need to specify when building your extension:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Package and release your extension</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/DISTRIBUTION/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/DISTRIBUTION/</guid>
      <description>This page contains additional information on how to package and distribute extensions.&#xA;Package your extension Docker extensions are packaged as Docker images. The entire extension runtime including the UI, backend services (host or VM), and any necessary binary must be included in the extension image. Every extension image must contain a metadata.json file at the root of its filesystem that defines the contents of the extension.&#xA;The Docker image must have several image labels, providing information about the extension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publish your extension in the Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/publish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/publish/</guid>
      <description>Submit your extension to the Marketplace Docker Desktop displays published extensions in the Extensions Marketplace on Docker Desktop and Docker Hub. The Extensions Marketplace is a space where developers can discover extensions to improve their developer experience and propose their own extension to be available for all Desktop users.&#xA;Whenever you are ready to publish your extension in the Marketplace, you can self-publish your extension&#xA;Note&#xA;As the Extension Marketplace continues to add new features for both Extension users and publishers, you are expected to maintain your extension over time to ensure it stays available in the Marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Share your extension</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/share/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/share/</guid>
      <description>Once your extension image is accessible on Docker Hub, anyone with access to the image can install the extension.&#xA;People can install your extension by typing docker extension install my/awesome-extension:latest in to the terminal.&#xA;However, this option doesn&#39;t provide a preview of the extension before it&#39;s installed.&#xA;Createa a share URL Docker lets you share your extensions using a URL.&#xA;When people navigate to this URL, it opens Docker Desktop and displays a preview of your extension in the same way as an extension in the Marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validate your extension</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/validate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/extensions/validate/</guid>
      <description>Validate your extension before you share or publish it. Validating the extension ensures that the extension:&#xA;Is built with the image labels it requires to display correctly in the marketplace Installs and runs without problems The Extensions CLI lets you validate your extension before installing and running it locally.&#xA;The validation checks if the extension’s Dockerfile specifies all the required labels and if the metadata file is valid against the JSON schema file.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
