<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UI styling overview for Docker extensions on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UI styling overview for Docker extensions on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design guidelines for Docker extensions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/design-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/design-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>At Docker, we aim to build tools that integrate into a user&#39;s existing workflows rather than requiring them to adopt new ones. We strongly recommend that you follow these guidelines when creating extensions. We review and approve your Marketplace publication based on these requirements.&#xA;Here is a simple checklist to go through when creating your extension:&#xA;Is it easy to get started? Is it easy to use? Is it easy to get help when needed?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker design principles</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/design-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/design-principles/</guid>
      <description>Provide actionable guidance We anticipate needs and provide simple explanations with clear actions so people are never lost and always know what to do next. Recommendations lead users to functionality that enhances the experience and extends their knowledge.&#xA;Create value through confidence People from all levels of experience should feel they know how to use our product. Experiences are familiar, unified, and easy to use so all users feel like experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUI best practices</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/mui-best-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/extensions-sdk/design/mui-best-practices/</guid>
      <description>This article assumes you&#39;re following our recommended practice by using our Material UI theme. Following the steps below maximises compatibility with Docker Desktop and minimises the work you need to do as an extension author. They should be considered supplementary to the non-MUI-specific guidelines found in the UI Styling overview.&#xA;Assume the theme can change at any time Resist the temptation to fine-tune your UI with precise colors, offsets and font sizings to make it look as attractive as possible.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
