<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contribute to Docker&#39;s docs on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contribute to Docker&#39;s docs on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accordions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/accordions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/accordions/</guid>
      <description> Example Accordion example $ docker run hello-world Markup {{&amp;lt; accordion title=&amp;#34;Accordion example&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} ```console $ docker run hello-world ``` {{&amp;lt; /accordion &amp;gt;}} </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Badges</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/badges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/badges/</guid>
      <description>Examples blue badge amber badge red badge green badge violet badge You can also make a badge a link.&#xA;badge with a link Usage guidelines We use the violet badge to highlight new content in our docs: New Best practice is to use this badge for no longer than 2 months post release of the feature.&#xA;Markup {{&amp;lt; badge color=amber text=&amp;#34;amber badge&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} [{{&amp;lt; badge color=&amp;#34;blue&amp;#34; text=&amp;#34;badge with a link&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}](.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttons</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/buttons/</guid>
      <description> Examples hello Markup {{&amp;lt; button url=&amp;#34;https://example.com/&amp;#34; text=&amp;#34;hello&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Callouts</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/call-outs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/call-outs/</guid>
      <description>We support these broad categories of callouts:&#xA;Version callouts Notes (no HTML attribute required) Tips, which use the { .tip } class Important, which use the { .important } class Warning, which use the { .warning } class Experimental, which use the { .experimental } class Restricted, which use the { .restricted } class Examples Introduced in Buildx version 0.10.4 Note&#xA;Note the way the get_hit_count function is written. This basic retry loop lets us attempt our request multiple times if the redis service is not available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cards</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/cards/</guid>
      <description>Cards can be added to a page using the card shortcode. The parameters for this shortcode are:&#xA;Parameter Description title The title of the card icon The icon slug of the card image Use a custom image instead of an icon (mutually exclusive with icon) link (Optional) The link target of the card, when clicked description A description text, in Markdown Note&#xA;There&#39;s a known limitation with the Markdown description of cards, in that they can&#39;t contain relative links, pointing to other .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code blocks</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/code-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/code-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Rouge provides lots of different code block &amp;quot;hints&amp;quot;. If you leave off the hint, it tries to guess and sometimes gets it wrong. These are just a few hints that we use often.&#xA;Variables If your example contains a placeholder value that&#39;s subject to change, use the format &amp;lt;[A-Z_]+&amp;gt; for the placeholder value: &amp;lt;MY_VARIABLE&amp;gt;&#xA;export name=&amp;lt;MY_NAME&amp;gt; This syntax is reserved for variable names, and will cause the variable to be rendered in a special color and font style.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker terminology</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/terminology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/terminology/</guid>
      <description>compose.yaml The current designation for the Compose file, as it&#39;s a file, format as code.&#xA;Compose plugin The compose plugin as an add-on (for Docker CLI) that can be enabled/disabled.&#xA;Digest A long string that’s automatically created every time you push an image. You can pull an image by Digest or by Tag.&#xA;Docker Compose Use when we talk about the application, or all the functionality associated with the application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formatting guide</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/formatting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/formatting/</guid>
      <description>Headings and subheadings Readers pay fractionally more attention to headings, bulleted lists, and links, so it&#39;s important to ensure the first two to three words in those items &amp;quot;front load&amp;quot; information as much as possible.&#xA;Best practice Headings and subheadings should let the reader know what they will find on the page. They should describe succinctly and accurately what the content is about. Headings should be short (no more than eight words), to the point and written in plain, active language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grammar and style</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/grammar/</guid>
      <description>Docker documentation should always be written in US English with US grammar.&#xA;Acronyms and initialisms An acronym is an abbreviation you would speak as a word, for example, ROM (for read only memory). Other examples include radar and scuba, which started out as acronyms but are now considered words in their own right.&#xA;An initialism is a type of acronym that comprises a group of initial letters used as an abbreviation for a name or expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icons</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/icons/</guid>
      <description>Below is an inventory of the icons we use to represent different topics or features across docs. To be used with the cards component.&#xA;Install Icon name = download FAQs Icon name = help Onboarding/quickstarts Icon name = explore Release notes Icon name = note_add Feedback Icon name = sms Multi-platform/arch Icon name = content_copy Rootless/ECI Icon name = security Settings management Icon name = shield_lock Processes Icon name = checklist Networking Icon name = network_node Exploring a feature Icon name = feature_search Company Icon name = apartment Organization Icon name = store Additional resources Icon name = category Designing Icon name = design_services Publishing Icon name = publish Interacting Icon name = multiple_stop Storage Icon name = database logs Icon name = feed Prune/cut Icon name = cut Configure Icon name = tune Deprecated Icon name = folder_delete RAM Icon name = home_storage IAM Icon name = photo_library Packaging Icon name = inventory_2 Multi-stage Icon name = stairs Architecture Icon name = construction Build drivers Icon name = engineering Export Icon name = output Cache Icon name = cycle Bake Icon name = cake Docker ID Icon name = fingerprint Repository Icon name = inbox Access tokens Icon name = password official images Icon name = verified Hardened Docker Desktop Icon name = lock Sign in Icon name = passkey SSO and SCIM Icon name = key 2FA Icon name = phonelink_lock Add/update payment method Icon name = credit_score Update billing info Icon name = contract_edit Billing history Icon name = payments Upgrade Icon name = upgrade Add/manage more seats/users Icon name = group_add Domains Icon name = domain_verification Company owner Icon name = supervised_user_circle General settings Icon name = settings </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/images/</guid>
      <description>Example A small image: Large images occupy the full width of the reading column by default:&#xA;Image size can be set using query parameters: ?h=&amp;lt;height&amp;gt;&amp;amp;w=&amp;lt;width&amp;gt;&#xA;Image with a border, also set with a query parameter: ?border=true&#xA;HTML and Markdown - A small image: ![a small image](/assets/images/footer_moby_icon.png) - Large images occupy the full width of the reading column by default: ![a pretty wide image](/assets/images/banner_image_24512.png) - Image size can be set using query parameters: `?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/links/</guid>
      <description>Examples External links open in a new tab Internal links open in the same tab You can use relative links, using source filenames, or you can use absolute links for pages as they appear on the final site.&#xA;Links to auto-generated content When you link to heading IDs in auto-generated pages, such as CLI reference content, you won&#39;t get any help from your editor in resolving the anchor names. That&#39;s because the pages are generated at build-time and your editor or LSP doesn&#39;t know about them in advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lists</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/lists/</guid>
      <description>Examples Use dashes (-) or asterisks (*) for bullet points.&#xA;Bullet list item 1 Bullet list item 2 Bullet list item 3 Numbered list item 1. Two spaces between the period and the first letter helps with alignment.&#xA;Numbered list item 2. Let&#39;s put a note in it.&#xA;Note: We did it!&#xA;Numbered list item 3 with a code block in it. You need the blank line before the code block happens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recommended word list</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/recommended-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/recommended-words/</guid>
      <description>To help ensure consistency across documentation, the Technical Writing team recommends these wording choices.&#xA;&amp;amp; (ampersand) Don&#39;t use &amp;amp; instead of and in headings, text, navigation, UI copy, or tables of contents.&#xA;above Try to avoid using above when referring to an example or table in a documentation page. If required, use previous instead.&#xA;For example:&#xA;In the previous example, the dog had fleas.&#xA;account name Don&#39;t use. Instead, use username.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source file conventions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/file-conventions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/file-conventions/</guid>
      <description>File name When you create a new .md file for new content, make sure:&#xA;File names are as short as possible Try to keep the file name to one word or two words Use a dash to separate words. For example: add-seats.md and remove-seats.md. multiplatform-images preferred to multi-platform-images. Front matter The front matter of a given page is in a section at the top of the Markdown file that starts and ends with three hyphens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tables</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/tables/</guid>
      <description>Example Basic table Permission level Access Bold or italic within a table cell. Next cell is empty on purpose. Previous cell is empty. A --flag in mono text. Read Pull Read/Write Pull, push Admin All of the above, plus update description, create, and delete Feature-support table Platform x86_64 / amd64 Ubuntu ✅ Debian ✅ Fedora Arch (btw) ✅ Markdown Basic table | Permission level | Access | | :----------------------------------------------------------------------- | :------------------------------------------------------------ | | **Bold** or _italic_ within a table cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tabs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/tabs/</guid>
      <description>The tabs component consists of two shortcodes:&#xA;{{&amp;lt; tabs &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; tab name=&amp;quot;name of the tab&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}} The {{&amp;lt; tabs &amp;gt;}} shortcode is a parent, component, wrapping a number of tabs. Each {{&amp;lt; tab &amp;gt;}} is given a name using the name attribute.&#xA;You can optionally specify a group attribute for the tabs wrapper to indicate that a tab section should belong to a group of tabs. See Groups.&#xA;Example JavaScript Go console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI elements in content</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/ui/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information on how to write technical content that involves a user interface (UI).&#xA;Format names of UI elements Always bold UI elements when referring to them by name.&#xA;This includes names for buttons, menus, dialogs, windows, list items, or any other feature on the page that has a visible name.&#xA;Don&#39;t make an official feature name or product name bold, except when it directly refers to an element on the page that uses the name, such as a window title or button name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/components/videos/</guid>
      <description>Video guidelines Videos are used rarely in Docker&#39;s documentation. When used, video should complement written text and not be the sole format of documentation. Videos can take longer to produce and be more difficult to maintain than written text or even screenshots, so consider the following before adding video:&#xA;Can you demonstrate a clear customer need for using video? Does the video offer new content, rather than directly reading or re-purposing official documentation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice and tone</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/voice-tone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/style/voice-tone/</guid>
      <description>Voice At Docker, we&#39;ve been the customer. We&#39;re developers developing for developers. We speak with experience and knowledge and without arrogance or ego. We want to inform and empower people without being confusing or pushy.&#xA;We&#39;re not afraid to use a bit of cheeky humor to lighten the conversation (and because we don&#39;t take ourselves too seriously) but we&#39;re always respectful. We communicate with clarity, empathy, and wit; everything we say should inform and encourage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing checklist</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/contribute/checklist/</guid>
      <description>Use this checklist to communicate in a way that is clear, helpful, and consistent with the rest of Docker Docs.&#xA;Used active voice Active voice is specific and removes ambiguity.&#xA;In active voice, the subject of the sentence (the customer or the system) does the action.&#xA;Sentences that use active voice are easier to read. Active voice makes it clear who has done what and to whom. Plus, active voice keeps sentences direct and more concise.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
