<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integrating Docker Scout with other systems on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Integrating Docker Scout with other systems on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artifactory integration</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/registry/artifactory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/registry/artifactory/</guid>
      <description>Integrating Docker Scout with JFrog Artifactory lets you run image analysis automatically on images in Artifactory registries.&#xA;Local image analysis You can analyze Artifactory images for vulnerabilities locally using Docker Desktop or the Docker CLI. You first need to authenticate with JFrog Artifactory using the docker login command. For example:&#xA;docker login {URL} Tip&#xA;For cloud-hosted Artifactory you can find the credentials for your Artifactory repository by selecting it in the Artifactory UI and then the Set Me Up button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Container Registry integration</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/registry/acr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/registry/acr/</guid>
      <description>Integrating Docker Scout with Azure Container Registry (ACR) lets you view image insights for images hosted in ACR repositories. After integrating Docker Scout with ACR and activating Docker Scout for a repository, pushing an image to the repository automatically triggers image analysis. You can view image insights using the Docker Scout Dashboard, or the docker scout CLI commands.&#xA;How it works To help you integrate your Azure Container Registry with Docker Scout, you can use a custom Azure Resource Manager (ARM) template that automatically creates the necessary infrastructure in Azure for you:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Docker Scout with Amazon ECR</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/registry/ecr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/registry/ecr/</guid>
      <description>Integrating Docker Scout with Amazon Elastic Container Registry (ECR) lets you view image insights for images hosted in ECR repositories. After integrating Docker Scout with ECR and activating Docker Scout for a repository, pushing an image to the repository automatically triggers image analysis. You can view image insights using the Docker Scout Dashboard, or the docker scout CLI commands.&#xA;How it works To help you integrate Docker Scout with ECR, you can use a CloudFormation stack template that creates and configures the necessary AWS resources for integrating Docker Scout with your ECR registry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Docker Scout with GitHub</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/source-code-management/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/source-code-management/github/</guid>
      <description>Beta feature&#xA;The GitHub integration is currently in Beta.&#xA;The GitHub app integration for Docker Scout grants Docker Scout access to your source code repository on GitHub. This improved visibility into how your image gets created means Docker Scout can give you automated and contextual remediation advice.&#xA;How it works When you enable the GitHub integration, Docker Scout can make a direct link between the image analysis results and the source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Docker Scout with Slack</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/team-collaboration/slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/team-collaboration/slack/</guid>
      <description>You can integrate Docker Scout with Slack by creating a Slack webhook and adding it to the Docker Scout Dashboard. Docker Scout will notify you about when a new vulnerability is disclosed, and it affects one or more of your images.&#xA;Example Slack notification from Docker Scout How it works After configuring the integration, Docker Scout sends notifications about changes to policy compliance and vulnerability exposure for your repositories, to the Slack channels associated with the webhook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Docker Scout with SonarQube</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/code-quality/sonarqube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/integrations/code-quality/sonarqube/</guid>
      <description>The SonarQube integration enables Docker Scout to surface SonarQube quality gate checks through Policy Evaluation, under a new Quality gates passed policy.&#xA;How it works This integration uses SonarQube webhooks to notify Docker Scout of when a SonarQube project analysis has completed. When the webhook is called, Docker Scout receives the analysis results, and stores them in the database.&#xA;When you push a new image to a repository, Docker Scout evaluates the results of the SonarQube analysis record corresponding to the image.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
