<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Securing your software supply chain with Docker Scout on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Securing your software supply chain with Docker Scout on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Docker Scout?</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/why/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Organizations face significant challenges from data breaches,&#xA;including financial losses, operational disruptions, and long-term damage to&#xA;brand reputation and customer trust. Docker Scout addresses critical problems&#xA;such as identifying insecure container images, preventing security breaches,&#xA;and reducing the risk of operational downtime due to vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Docker Scout provides several benefits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Secure and trusted content&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A system of record for your Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Continuous security posture improvement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Docker Scout offers automated vulnerability detection and remediation, helping&#xA;organizations identify and fix security issues in container images early in the&#xA;development process. It also integrates with popular development tools like&#xA;Docker Desktop and GitHub Actions, providing seamless security management and&#xA;compliance checks within existing workflows.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Scout demo</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/demo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Docker Scout has powerful features for enhancing containerized application&#xA;security and ensuring a robust software supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Define vulnerability remediation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discuss why remediation is essential to maintain the security and integrity&#xA;of containerized applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discuss common vulnerabilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Implement remediation techniques: updating base images, applying patches,&#xA;removing unnecessary packages&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Verify and validate remediation efforts using Docker Scout&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div id=&#34;youtube-player-TkLwJ0p46W8&#34; data-video-id=&#34;TkLwJ0p46W8&#34; class=&#34;youtube-video aspect-video h-fit w-full py-2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div id=&#34;scout-lp-survey-anchor&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common challenges and questions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/common-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-scout/common-questions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- vale Docker.HeadingLength = NO --&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34; scroll-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;how-is-docker-scout-different-from-other-security-tools&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;text-black dark:text-white no-underline hover:underline&#34; href=&#34;#how-is-docker-scout-different-from-other-security-tools&#34;&gt;&#xA;    How is Docker Scout different from other security tools?&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Docker Scout takes a broader approach to container security compared to&#xA;third-party security tools. Third-party security tools, if they offer&#xA;remediation guidance at all, miss the mark on their limited scope of&#xA;application security posture within the software supply chain, and often&#xA;limited guidance when it comes to suggested fixes. Such tools have either&#xA;limitations on runtime monitoring or no runtime protection at all. When they do&#xA;offer runtime monitoring, it’s limited in its adherence to key policies.&#xA;Third-party security tools offer a limited scope of policy evaluation for&#xA;Docker-specific builds. By focusing on the entire software supply chain,&#xA;providing actionable guidance, and offering comprehensive runtime protection&#xA;with strong policy enforcement, Docker Scout goes beyond just identifying&#xA;vulnerabilities in your containers. It helps you build secure applications from&#xA;the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
