<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Container security FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/containers/</guid>
      <description>How are containers isolated from the host in Docker Desktop? Docker Desktop runs all containers inside a customized / minimal Linux virtual machine (except for native Windows containers). This adds a strong layer of isolation between containers and the host the machine, even if containers are running rootful.&#xA;However note the following:&#xA;Containers have access to host files configured for file sharing via Settings -&amp;gt; Resources -&amp;gt; File Sharing (see the next FAQ question below for more info).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and manage access tokens</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-developers/access-tokens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-developers/access-tokens/</guid>
      <description>You can create a personal access token (PAT) to use as an alternative to your password for Docker CLI authentication.&#xA;Compared to passwords, PATs provide the following advantages:&#xA;You can investigate when the PAT was last used and then disable or delete it if you find any suspicious activity. When using an access token, you can&#39;t perform any admin activity on the account, including changing the password. It protects your account if your computer is compromised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker security announcements</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/security-announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/security-announcements/</guid>
      <description>Docker Security Advisory: Multiple Vulnerabilities in runc, BuildKit, and Moby Last updated February 2, 2024&#xA;We at Docker prioritize the security and integrity of our software and the trust of our users. Security researchers at Snyk Labs identified and reported four security vulnerabilities in the container ecosystem. One of the vulnerabilities, CVE-2024-21626, concerns the runc container runtime, and the other three affect BuildKit ( CVE-2024-23651, CVE-2024-23652, and CVE-2024-23653). We want to assure our community that our team, in collaboration with the reporters and open source maintainers, has been diligently working on coordinating and implementing necessary remediations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain audit</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/domain-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/domain-audit/</guid>
      <description>Domain audit identifies uncaptured users in an organization. Uncaptured users are Docker users who have authenticated to Docker using an email address associated with one of your verified domains, but they&#39;re not a member of your organization in Docker. You can audit domains on organizations that are part of the Docker Business subscription. To upgrade your existing account to a Docker Business subscription, see Upgrade your subscription.&#xA;Uncaptured users who access Docker Desktop in your environment may pose a security risk because your organization&#39;s security settings, like Image Access Management and Registry Access Management, aren&#39;t applied to a user&#39;s session.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domains</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/domain-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/domain-faqs/</guid>
      <description>Can I add sub-domains? Yes, you can add sub-domains to your SSO connection, however all email addresses should also be on that domain. Verify that your DNS provider supports multiple TXT records for the same domain.&#xA;Can the DNS provider configure it once for one-time verification and remove it later or will it be needed permanently? You can do it one time to add the domain to a connection. If your organization ever changes IdPs and has to set up SSO again, your DNS provider will need to verify again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enforce sign-in for Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/configure-sign-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/configure-sign-in/</guid>
      <description>By default, members of your organization can use Docker Desktop without signing in. When users don’t sign in as a member of your organization, they don’t receive the benefits of your organization’s subscription and they can circumvent Docker’s security features for your organization.&#xA;To ensure members of your organization always sign in, you can deploy a registry.json configuration file to the machines of your users.&#xA;How is sign-in enforced? When Docker Desktop starts and it detects a registry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enforcement</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/enforcement-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/enforcement-faqs/</guid>
      <description>We currently have a Docker Team subscription. How do we enable SSO? SSO is available with a Docker Business subscription. To enable SSO, you must first upgrade your subscription to a Docker Business subscription. To learn how to upgrade your existing account, see Upgrade your subscription.&#xA;How do service accounts work with SSO? Service accounts work like any other user when SSO is turned on. If the service account is using an email for a domain with SSO turned on, it needs a PAT for CLI and API usage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General FAQs on SSO</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/faqs/</guid>
      <description>Is Docker SSO available for all paid subscriptions? Docker single sign-on (SSO) is only available with the Docker Business subscription. Upgrade your existing subscription to start using Docker SSO.&#xA;How does Docker SSO work? Docker SSO lets users authenticate using their identity providers (IdPs) to access Docker. Docker supports Entra ID (formerly Azure AD) and any SAML 2.0 identity providers. When you enable SSO, this redirects users to your provider’s authentication page to authenticate using their email and password.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General security FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/general/</guid>
      <description>How do I report a vulnerability? If you’ve discovered a security vulnerability in Docker, we encourage you to report it responsibly. Report security issues to security@docker.com so that they can be quickly addressed by our team.&#xA;How are passwords managed when SSO isn&#39;t used? Passwords are encrypted and salt-hashed. If you use application-level passwords instead of SSO, you are responsible for ensuring that your employees know how to pick strong passwords, don&#39;t share passwords, and don&#39;t reuse passwords across multiple systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group mapping</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/provisioning/group-mapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/provisioning/group-mapping/</guid>
      <description>With directory group-to-team provisioning from your IdP, user updates will automatically sync with your Docker organizations and teams. You can use group mapping once you have configured single sign-on (SSO).&#xA;Tip&#xA;Group mapping is ideal for adding a user to multiple organizations or multiple teams within one organization. If you don&#39;t need to set up multi-organization or multi-team assignment, you can use user-level attributes.&#xA;How group mapping works IdPs share with Docker the main attributes of every authorized user through SSO, such as email address, name, surname, and groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity providers</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/idp-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/idp-faqs/</guid>
      <description>Is it possible to use more than one IdP with Docker SSO? No. You can only configure Docker SSO to work with a single IdP. A domain can only be associated with a single IdP. Docker supports Entra ID (formerly Azure AD) and identity providers that support SAML 2.0.&#xA;Is it possible to change my identity provider after configuring SSO? Yes. You must delete your existing IdP configuration in your Docker SSO connection and then configure SSO using your new IdP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Access Management</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/image-access-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/image-access-management/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Image Access Management is available to Docker Business customers only.&#xA;Image Access Management gives administrators control over which types of images, such as Docker Official Images, Docker Verified Publisher Images, or community images, their developers can pull from Docker Hub.&#xA;For example, a developer, who is part of an organization, building a new containerized application could accidentally use an untrusted, community image as a component of their application. This image could be malicious and pose a security risk to the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just-in-Time provisioning</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/provisioning/just-in-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/provisioning/just-in-time/</guid>
      <description>Just-in-Time (JIT) provisioning runs after every successful single sign-on (SSO) sign-in. JIT verifies that the user that signs in is a member of the organization and teams that they are assigned to in the IdP. When you create your SSO connection, JIT provisioning is turned on by default.&#xA;SSO authentication with JIT provisioning enabled After every successful SSO sign-in authentication, the JIT provisioner performs the following actions:&#xA;Checks if there&#39;s an existing Docker account with the email address of the user that just authenticated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage users</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/users-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/single-sign-on/users-faqs/</guid>
      <description>How do I manage users when using SSO? You can manage users through organizations in Docker Hub or Admin Console. When you configure SSO in Docker, you need to make sure an account exists for each user in your IdP account. When a user signs in to Docker for the first time using their domain email address, they will be automatically added to the organization after a successful authentication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network and VM FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/networking-and-vms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/faqs/networking-and-vms/</guid>
      <description>How can I limit the type of internet access allowed by the container when it runs, to prevent it from being able to exfiltrate data or download malicious code? There is no built-in mechanism for that but it can be addressed by process-level firewall on the host. Hook into the com.docker.vpnkit user-space process and apply rules where it can connect to (DNS URL white list; packet/payload filter) and which ports/protocols it is allowed to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registry Access Management</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/registry-access-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/registry-access-management/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Registry Access Management is available to Docker Business customers only.&#xA;With Registry Access Management (RAM), administrators can ensure that their developers using Docker Desktop only access allowed registries. This is done through the Registry Access Management dashboard in Docker Hub or the Docker Admin Console.&#xA;Registry Access Management supports both cloud and on-prem registries. This feature operates at the DNS level and therefore is compatible with all registries. You can add any hostname or domain name you’d like to include in the list of allowed registries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roles and permissions</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/roles-and-permissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/roles-and-permissions/</guid>
      <description>Organization and company owners can assign roles to individuals giving them different permissions in the organization. This section is for owners who want to learn about the defined roles and their permission scopes.&#xA;Roles When you invite users to your organization, you assign a role. A role is a collection of permissions. Roles define access to perform actions like creating repositories, pulling images, creating teams, and configuring organization settings.&#xA;The following roles are available to assign:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIM provisioning</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/provisioning/scim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/security/for-admins/provisioning/scim/</guid>
      <description>This section is for administrators who want to enable System for Cross-domain Identity Management (SCIM) 2.0 for their business. It is available for Docker Business customers.&#xA;SCIM provides automated user provisioning and de-provisioning for your Docker organization or company through your identity provider (IdP). Once you enable SCIM in Docker and your IdP, any user assigned to the Docker application in the IdP is automatically provisioned in Docker and added to the organization or company.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
