<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release notes on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/tags/release-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release notes on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/tags/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the new features, improvements, and bug fixes in Docker Buildx.&#xA;0.16.0 2024-07-11 The full release note for this release is available on GitHub.&#xA;New Bake command now supports --call and --check flags and call attribute in target definitions for selecting custom frontend methods. docker/buildx#2556, docker/buildx#2576 Experimental Bake now supports --list-targets and --list-variables flags for inspecting the definition and possible configuration options for your project. docker/buildx#2556 Bake definition variables and targets supports new description attribute for defining text-based description that can be inspected using e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>For more detailed information, see the release notes in the Compose repo.&#xA;2.29.0 2024-07-17 Update Dependencies upgrade: bump compose-go to v2.1.4 Dependencies upgrade: bump docker engine and cli to v27.0.3 Dependencies upgrade: bump buildx to 0.16.0 Dependencies upgrade: bump buildkit to 0.15.0 Dependencies upgrade: bump containerd to 1.7.19 Bug fixes and enhancements Added a JSON stream progress writer. Added a --prune flag to the docker compose watch command. Unnecessary resources are now excluded after services have been selected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the new features, improvements, known issues, and bug fixes in Docker Desktop releases. For frequently asked questions about Docker Desktop releases, see FAQs.&#xA;Docker Desktop versions older than 6 months from the latest release are not available for download.&#xA;Take a look at the Docker Public Roadmap to see what&#39;s coming next.&#xA;4.32.0 2024-07-04 Download Docker Desktop&#xA;Windows (checksum) | Windows ARM Beta (checksum) | Mac with Apple chip (checksum) | Mac with Intel chip (checksum) | Debian - RPM - Arch (checksum)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Engine 27.0 release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/engine/release-notes/27.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/engine/release-notes/27.0/</guid>
      <description>This page describes the latest changes, additions, known issues, and fixes for Docker Engine version 27.0.&#xA;For more information about:&#xA;Deprecated and removed features, see Deprecated Engine Features. Changes to the Engine API, see Engine API version history. 27.0.3 2024-07-01 For a full list of pull requests and changes in this release, refer to the relevant GitHub milestones:&#xA;docker/cli, 27.0.3 milestone moby/moby, 27.0.3 milestone Deprecated and removed features, see Deprecated Features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hub release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Here you can learn about the latest changes, new features, bug fixes, and known issues for each Docker Hub release.&#xA;Take a look at the Docker Public Roadmap to see what&#39;s coming next.&#xA;2024-03-23 New You can tag Docker Hub repositories with categories. 2023-12-11 The Advanced Image Management feature, along with the corresponding API endpoints, has been retired. See docker/roadmap#534.&#xA;The following API endpoints have been removed:&#xA;/namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images /namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images/{digest}/tags /namespaces/{namespace}/repositories/{repository}/images-summary /namespaces/{namespace}/delete-images 2023-08-28 Organizations with SSO enabled can assign members to roles, organizations, and teams with SCIM role mapping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Scout release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/release-notes/platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/scout/release-notes/platform/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the new features, improvements, known issues, and bug fixes in Docker Scout releases. These release notes cover the Docker Scout platform, including the Dashboard. For CLI release notes, refer to Docker Scout CLI release notes.&#xA;Take a look at the Docker Public Roadmap for what&#39;s coming next.&#xA;Q2 2024 New features and enhancements released in the second quarter of 2024.&#xA;2024-05-0x This release introduces initial support for Exceptions in the Docker Scout Dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dockerfile release notes</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/dockerfile/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/build/dockerfile/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the new features, improvements, known issues, and bug fixes in Dockerfile reference.&#xA;For usage, see the Dockerfile frontend syntax page.&#xA;1.9.0 2024-07-11 The full release note for this release is available on GitHub.&#xA;# syntax=docker/dockerfile:1.9.0 Add new validation rules: SecretsUsedInArgOrEnv InvalidDefaultArgInFrom RedundantTargetPlatform CopyIgnoredFile (experimental) FromPlatformFlagConstDisallowed Many performance improvements for working with big Dockerfiles. moby/buildkit#5067, moby/buildkit#5029 Fix possible panic when building Dockerfile without defined stages. moby/buildkit#5150 Fix incorrect JSON parsing that could cause some incorrect JSON values to pass without producing an error.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
