<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker subscription overview on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker subscription overview on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Add seats to your subscription</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/add-seats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/add-seats/</guid>
      <description>Important&#xA;Starting July 1, 2024, Docker will begin collecting sales tax on subscription fees in compliance with state regulations for customers in the United States. For our global customers subject to VAT, the implementation will start rolling out on July 1, 2024. Note that while the rollout begins on this date, VAT charges may not apply to all applicable subscriptions immediately.&#xA;To ensure that tax assessments are correct, make sure that your billing information and VAT/Tax ID, if applicable, are updated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Core subscriptions and features</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/details/</guid>
      <description>You can do more with Docker with a Docker Core subscription, such as add collaborators, create scoped access tokens, and create private repositories. This page provides an overview of each subscription tier. To compare features available in each tier, see Docker Pricing.&#xA;The following describes some of the key features included with your Docker Core subscription:&#xA;3 Docker Scout-enabled repositories for advanced remote image analysis. You can purchase a Docker Scout subscription to enable more repositories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop license agreement</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/desktop-license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/desktop-license/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop is licensed under the Docker Subscription Service Agreement. When you download and install Docker Desktop, you will be asked to agree to the updated terms.&#xA;Our Docker Subscription Service Agreement states:&#xA;Docker Desktop is free for small businesses (fewer than 250 employees AND less than $10 million in annual revenue), personal use, education, and non-commercial open source projects. Otherwise, it requires a paid subscription for professional use. Paid subscriptions are also required for government entities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Scout subscriptions and features</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/scout-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/scout-details/</guid>
      <description>This page provides an overview of the subscription plans for Docker Scout. To compare features available for each plan, see Docker Scout Pricing.&#xA;Docker Scout Free Docker Scout Free is available for both personal accounts and organizations. If you have a Docker subscription, you automatically have access to Docker Scout Free. This plan is ideal for individual developers getting started with software supply chain security.&#xA;Docker Scout Free includes:&#xA;Unlimited local image analysis Up to 3 Docker Scout-enabled repositories SDLC integration, including policy evaluation and workload integration On-prem and cloud container registry integrations Security posture reporting Docker Scout Team Docker Scout Team is available for both personal accounts and organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Downgrade your subscription</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/downgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/downgrade/</guid>
      <description>You can downgrade your Docker subscription at anytime before the renewal date. The unused portion of the subscription isn&#39;t refundable or creditable.&#xA;When you downgrade your subscription, access to paid features is available until the next billing cycle. The downgrade takes effect on the next billing cycle.&#xA;Important&#xA;If you downgrade your personal account from a Pro subscription to a Personal subscription, note that Personal subscriptions don&#39;t include collaborators for private repositories, and only 1 private repository is included.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage seats and invites</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/build-cloud/manage-seats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/build-cloud/manage-seats/</guid>
      <description>You can add seats and manage invitations to your Docker Build Cloud Team in the Docker Build Cloud dashboard.&#xA;Note&#xA;If you have a Docker Build Cloud Business subscription, you can add and remove seats by working with your account executive, then assign your purchased seats in the Docker Build Cloud dashboard.&#xA;Add seats Sign in to Docker Build Cloud. Select Settings &amp;amp; billing. Under your current plan, select Add seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove seats from your subscription</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/remove-seats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/remove-seats/</guid>
      <description>You can remove seats from your Team or Business subscription at anytime.&#xA;If you remove seats in the middle of the billing cycle, changes apply in the next billing cycle. Any unused portion of the subscription for removed seats isn&#39;t refundable or creditable.&#xA;For example, if you receive your billing on the 8th of every month for 10 seats and you want to remove 2 seats on the 15th of the month, the 2 seats will be removed from your subscription the next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subscription FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/faq/</guid>
      <description>For more information on Docker subscriptions, see Docker subscription overview.&#xA;Can I transfer my subscription from one user or organization account to another? Subscriptions are non-transferable.&#xA;Can I pause or delay my Docker subscription? You can&#39;t pause or delay a subscription, but you can downgrade. If a subscription invoice hasn&#39;t been paid on the due date, there&#39;s a 15 day grace period, including the due date.&#xA;Does Docker offer academic pricing?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subscriptions and features</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/build-cloud/build-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/build-cloud/build-details/</guid>
      <description>You can enhance your teams&#39; builds with a Build Cloud subscription. This page describes the features available for the different subscription tiers. To compare features available for each tier, see Docker Build Cloud pricing.&#xA;Docker Build Cloud Starter If you have an existing Docker Core subscription, a base level of Build Cloud minutes and cache are included. The features available vary depending on your Docker Core subscription tier.&#xA;Docker Personal 50 build minutes every month Available for one user 1 parallel build Docker Pro 100 build minutes every month Available for one user 4 parallel builds Docker Team 400 build minutes every month shared across your organization Option to onboard up to 100 members Can buy additional seats to add more minutes Docker Business All the features listed for Docker Team 800 build minutes every month shared across your organization Docker Build Cloud Team You can buy Docker Build Cloud Team if you don’t have a Docker Core subscription, or upgrade any Docker Core tier to enhance your developers&#39; experience with the following features:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade your subscription</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/core-subscription/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Important&#xA;Starting July 1, 2024, Docker will begin collecting sales tax on subscription fees in compliance with state regulations for customers in the United States. For our global customers subject to VAT, the implementation will start rolling out on July 1, 2024. Note that while the rollout begins on this date, VAT charges may not apply to all applicable subscriptions immediately.&#xA;To ensure that tax assessments are correct, make sure that your billing information and VAT/Tax ID, if applicable, are updated.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
