<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Administration overview on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Administration overview on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Convert an account into an organization</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/convert-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/convert-account/</guid>
      <description>You can convert an existing user account to an organization. This is useful if you need multiple users to access your account and the repositories that it’s connected to. Converting it to an organization gives you better control over permissions for these users through teams and roles.&#xA;When you convert a user account to an organization, the account is migrated to a Docker Team plan.&#xA;Important&#xA;Once you convert your account to an organization, you can’t revert it to a user account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deactivating an account or an organization</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/deactivate-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/deactivate-account/</guid>
      <description>You can deactivate an account at any time.&#xA;Warning&#xA;All Docker products and services that use your Docker account or organization account will be inaccessible after deactivating your account.&#xA;Deactivate a user account Prerequisites Before deactivating your Docker account, ensure that you meet the following requirements:&#xA;You must not be a member of a company or any teams or organizations. You must remove the account from all teams, organizations, or the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs on companies</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/faqs/company-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/faqs/company-faqs/</guid>
      <description>Are existing subscriptions affected when you create a company and add organizations to it? You can manage subscriptions and related billing details at the organization level.&#xA;Some of my organizations don’t have a Docker Business subscription. Can I still use a parent company? Yes, but you can only add organizations with a Docker Business subscription to a company.&#xA;What happens if one of my organizations downgrades from Docker Business, but I still need access as a company owner?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs on organizations</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/faqs/organization-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/faqs/organization-faqs/</guid>
      <description>What if the Docker ID I want for my organization or company is taken? All Docker IDs are first-come, first-served except for companies that have a US Trademark on a username. If you have a trademark for your namespace, Docker Support can retrieve the Docker ID for you.&#xA;How do I add an organization owner? An existing owner can add additional team members as organization owners. You can invite a member and assign them the owner role in Docker Hub or the Docker Admin Console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General FAQs for Docker accounts</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/admin/faqs/general-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/admin/faqs/general-faqs/</guid>
      <description>What is a Docker ID? A Docker ID is a username for your Docker account that lets you access Docker products. All you need is an email address to create a Docker ID, or you can sign up with your Google or GitHub account. Your Docker ID must be between 4 and 30 characters long, and can only contain numbers and lowercase letters. You can&#39;t use any special characters or spaces.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
