<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Troubleshooting on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/tags/troubleshooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Troubleshooting on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/tags/troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Known issues</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/known-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/known-issues/</guid>
      <description>For all platforms For Mac with Intel chip For Mac with Apple silicon IPv6 is not yet supported on Docker Desktop. The Mac Activity Monitor reports that Docker is using twice the amount of memory it&#39;s actually using. This is due to a bug in MacOS. We have written a detailed report on this.&#xA;Force-ejecting the .dmg after running Docker.app from it can cause the whale icon to become unresponsive, Docker tasks to show as not responding in the Activity Monitor, and for some processes to consume a large amount of CPU resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/overview/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information on how to diagnose and troubleshoot Docker Desktop, and how to check the logs.&#xA;Troubleshoot menu To navigate to Troubleshoot either:&#xA;Select the Docker menu and then Troubleshoot Select the Troubleshoot icon near the top-right corner of Docker Dashboard The Troubleshoot page contains the following options:&#xA;Restart Docker Desktop.&#xA;Get support. Users with a paid Docker subscription can use this option to send a support request. Other users can use this option to diagnose any issues in Docker Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot topics for Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/topics/</guid>
      <description>Tip&#xA;If you do not find a solution in troubleshooting, browse the GitHub repositories or create a new issue:&#xA;docker/for-mac docker/for-win docker/for-linux Topics for all platforms Make sure certificates are set up correctly Docker Desktop ignores certificates listed under insecure registries, and does not send client certificates to them. Commands like docker run that attempt to pull from the registry produces error messages on the command line, like this:&#xA;Error response from daemon: Get http://192.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot your autobuilds</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/troubleshoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/troubleshoot/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Automated builds require a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;Failing builds If a build fails, a Retry icon appears next to the build report line on the General and Builds tabs. The Build report page and Timeline logs also display a Retry button.&#xA;Note&#xA;If you are viewing the build details for a repository that belongs to an organization, the Cancel and Retry buttons only appear if you have Read &amp;amp; Write access to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting the Docker daemon</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/config/daemon/troubleshoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/config/daemon/troubleshoot/</guid>
      <description>This page describes how to troubleshoot and debug the daemon if you run into issues.&#xA;You can turn on debugging on the daemon to learn about the runtime activity of the daemon and to aid in troubleshooting. If the daemon is unresponsive, you can also force a full stack trace of all threads to be added to the daemon log by sending the SIGUSR signal to the Docker daemon.&#xA;Daemon Unable to connect to the Docker daemon Cannot connect to the Docker daemon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workarounds for common problems</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/workarounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/troubleshoot/workarounds/</guid>
      <description>Reboot Restart your PC to stop / discard any vestige of the daemon running from the previously installed version.&#xA;Unset DOCKER_HOST The DOCKER_HOST environmental variable does not need to be set. If you use bash, use the command unset ${!DOCKER_*} to unset it. For other shells, consult the shell&#39;s documentation.&#xA;Make sure Docker is running for webserver examples For the hello-world-nginx example and others, Docker Desktop must be running to get to the webserver on http://localhost/.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
