<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get started with Policy Evaluation in Docker Scout on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get started with Policy Evaluation in Docker Scout on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Configure policies</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/configure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/configure/</guid>
      <description>Some of the existing policies are configurable. This means that you can clone an existing policy and create new, custom policies with your own configuration. You can also disable a policy altogether, if a policy doesn&#39;t quite match your needs.&#xA;Configure a policy To change the configuration of a policy, you must clone one of the existing default policies, and then save your configuration as a new policy. You can edit the display name and description of the new policy to help distinguish it from the default policy it&#39;s based on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Scout health scores</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/scores/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/scores/</guid>
      <description>Beta&#xA;Health scores is a Beta feature of Docker Scout. The feature is only available to organizations selected to participate in the early access program.&#xA;Docker Scout health scores provide a security assessment, and overall supply chain health, of images on Docker Hub, helping you determine whether an image meets established security best practices. The scores range from A to F, where A represents the highest level of security and F the lowest, offering an at-a-glance view of the security posture of your images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluate policy compliance in CI</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/ci/</guid>
      <description>Adding Policy Evaluation to your continuous integration pipelines helps you detect and prevent cases where code changes would cause policy compliance to become worse compared to your baseline.&#xA;The recommended strategy for Policy Evaluation in a CI setting involves evaluating a local image and comparing the results to a baseline. If the policy compliance for the local image is worse than the specified baseline, the CI run fails with an error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remediation with Docker Scout</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/remediation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/remediation/</guid>
      <description>Beta feature&#xA;Remediation with Docker Scout is currently in Beta.&#xA;Docker Scout helps you remediate supply chain or security issues by providing recommendations based on policy evaluation results. Recommendations are suggested actions you can take that improve policy compliance, or that add metadata to images which enables Docker Scout to provide better evaluation results and recommendations.&#xA;Docker Scout provides remediation advice for the following policies:&#xA;Outdated base images Supply chain attestations For images that violate policy, the recommendations focus on addressing compliance issues and fixing violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View Docker Scout policy status</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/scout/policy/view/</guid>
      <description>Early Access&#xA;Policy Evaluation is an Early Access feature of Docker Scout.&#xA;You can track policy status for your artifacts from the Docker Scout Dashboard, or using the CLI.&#xA;Dashboard The Overview tab of the Docker Scout Dashboard displays a summary of recent changes in policy for your repositories. This summary shows images that have seen the most change in their policy evaluation between the most recent image and the previous image.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
