<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage repositories on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage repositories on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Access repositories</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/access/</guid>
      <description>Within your repository, you can give others access to push and pull to your repository, and you can assign permissions. You can also view your repository tags and the associated images.&#xA;Collaborators and their role A collaborator is someone you want to give access to a private repository. Once designated, they can push and pull to your repositories. They&#39;re not allowed to perform any administrative tasks such as deleting the repository or changing its status from private to public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Categories in Docker Hub</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/categories/</guid>
      <description>You can tag Docker Hub repositories with categories, representing the primary intended use cases for your images. This lets users more easily find and explore content for the problem domain that they&#39;re interested in.&#xA;Available categories The Docker Hub content team maintains a curated list of categories. The available categories are:&#xA;API Management: Tools for creating, publishing, analyzing, and securing APIs. Content Management System: Software applications to create and manage digital content through templates, procedures, and standard formats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create repositories</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/create/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/docker-hub/repos/create/</guid>
      <description>Repositories let you share container images with your team, customers, or the Docker community at large.&#xA;A single Docker Hub repository can hold many Docker images which are stored as tags. You can push Docker images to Docker Hub with the docker pushcommand.&#xA;Create a repository Sign in to Docker Hub. Select Repositories. Near the top-right corner, select Create Repository. When creating a new repository:&#xA;You can choose to locate it under your own user account, or under any organization where you are an owner or editor.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
