<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FAQ on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/tags/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FAQ on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/tags/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Billing FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/billing/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/billing/faqs/</guid>
      <description>For more information on billing, see Billing and payments.&#xA;What credit and debit cards are supported? Visa MasterCard American Express Discover JCB Diners UnionPay What currency is supported? United States dollar (USD).&#xA;What happens if my subscription payment fails? If your subscription payment fails, there is a grace period of 15 days, including the due date. Docker retries to collect the payment 3 times using the following schedule:&#xA;3 days after the due date 5 days after the previous attempt 7 days after the previous attempt Docker also sends an email notification Action Required - Credit Card Payment Failed with an attached unpaid invoice after each failed payment attempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compose FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is the difference between docker compose and docker-compose Version one of the Docker Compose command-line binary was first released in 2014. It was written in Python, and is invoked with docker-compose. Typically, Compose V1 projects include a top-level version element in the compose.yml file, with values ranging from 2.0 to 3.8, which refer to the specific file formats.&#xA;Version two of the Docker Compose command-line binary was announced in 2020, is written in Go, and is invoked with docker compose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Container security FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/containers/</guid>
      <description>How are containers isolated from the host in Docker Desktop? Docker Desktop runs all containers inside a customized / minimal Linux virtual machine (except for native Windows containers). This adds a strong layer of isolation between containers and the host the machine, even if containers are running rootful.&#xA;However note the following:&#xA;Containers have access to host files configured for file sharing via Settings -&amp;gt; Resources -&amp;gt; File Sharing (see the next FAQ question below for more info).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domains</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/domain-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/domain-faqs/</guid>
      <description>Can I add sub-domains? Yes, you can add sub-domains to your SSO connection, however all email addresses should also be on that domain. Verify that your DNS provider supports multiple TXT records for the same domain.&#xA;Can the DNS provider configure it once for one-time verification and remove it later or will it be needed permanently? You can do it one time to add the domain to a connection. If your organization ever changes IdPs and has to set up SSO again, your DNS provider will need to verify again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enforcement</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/enforcement-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/enforcement-faqs/</guid>
      <description>We currently have a Docker Team subscription. How do we enable SSO? SSO is available with a Docker Business subscription. To enable SSO, you must first upgrade your subscription to a Docker Business subscription. To learn how to upgrade your existing account, see Upgrade your subscription.&#xA;How do service accounts work with SSO? Service accounts work like any other user when SSO is turned on. If the service account is using an email for a domain with SSO turned on, it needs a PAT for CLI and API usage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs for Docker Desktop for Linux</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/linuxfaqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/linuxfaqs/</guid>
      <description>Why does Docker Desktop for Linux run a VM? Docker Desktop for Linux runs a Virtual Machine (VM) for the following reasons:&#xA;To ensure that Docker Desktop provides a consistent experience across platforms.&#xA;During research, the most frequently cited reason for users wanting Docker Desktop for Linux was to ensure a consistent Docker Desktop experience with feature parity across all major operating systems. Utilizing a VM ensures that the Docker Desktop experience for Linux users will closely match that of Windows and macOS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs for Docker Desktop for Mac</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/macfaqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/macfaqs/</guid>
      <description>What is HyperKit? HyperKit is a hypervisor built on top of the Hypervisor.framework in macOS. It runs entirely in userspace and has no other dependencies.&#xA;We use HyperKit to eliminate the need for other VM products, such as Oracle VirtualBox or VMWare Fusion.&#xA;What is the benefit of HyperKit? HyperKit is thinner than VirtualBox and VMWare fusion, and the version included is customized for Docker workloads on Mac.&#xA;Why is com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs for Docker Desktop for Windows</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/windowsfaqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/windowsfaqs/</guid>
      <description>Can I use VirtualBox alongside Docker Desktop? Yes, you can run VirtualBox along with Docker Desktop if you have enabled the Windows Hypervisor Platform feature on your machine.&#xA;Why is Windows 10 or Windows 11 required? Docker Desktop uses the Windows Hyper-V features. While older Windows versions have Hyper-V, their Hyper-V implementations lack features critical for Docker Desktop to work.&#xA;Can I run Docker Desktop on Windows Server? No, running Docker Desktop on Windows Server is not supported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs on companies</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/faqs/company-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/faqs/company-faqs/</guid>
      <description>Are existing subscriptions affected when you create a company and add organizations to it? You can manage subscriptions and related billing details at the organization level.&#xA;Some of my organizations don’t have a Docker Business subscription. Can I still use a parent company? Yes, but you can only add organizations with a Docker Business subscription to a company.&#xA;What happens if one of my organizations downgrades from Docker Business, but I still need access as a company owner?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs on Docker Desktop releases</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/releases/</guid>
      <description>How frequent will new releases be? New releases are available roughly every month, unless there are critical fixes that need to be released sooner.&#xA;The Automatically check for updates setting in the Software updates tab is turned on by default. This means you receive notifications in the Docker menu and a notification badge on the Docker Dashboard when a new version is available.&#xA;You can also let Docker Desktop automatically download new updates in the background by selecting the Always download updates checkbox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs on organizations</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/faqs/organization-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/faqs/organization-faqs/</guid>
      <description>What if the Docker ID I want for my organization or company is taken? All Docker IDs are first-come, first-served except for companies that have a US Trademark on a username. If you have a trademark for your namespace, Docker Support can retrieve the Docker ID for you.&#xA;How do I add an organization owner? An existing owner can add additional team members as organization owners. You can invite a member and assign them the owner role in Docker Hub or the Docker Admin Console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General FAQs for Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/faqs/general/</guid>
      <description>Can I use Docker Desktop offline? Yes, you can use Docker Desktop offline. However, you cannot access features that require an active internet connection. Additionally, any functionality that requires you to sign in won&#39;t work while using Docker Desktop offline or in air-gapped environments. This includes:&#xA;The resources in the Learning Center Pulling or pushing an image to Docker Hub Image Access Management Static vulnerability scanning Viewing remote images in the Docker Dashboard Setting up Dev Environments Docker Build when using BuildKit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General FAQs for Docker accounts</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/faqs/general-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/admin/faqs/general-faqs/</guid>
      <description>What is a Docker ID? A Docker ID is a username for your Docker account that lets you access Docker products. All you need is an email address to create a Docker ID, or you can sign up with your Google or GitHub account. Your Docker ID must be between 4 and 30 characters long, and can only contain numbers and lowercase letters. You can&#39;t use any special characters or spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General FAQs on SSO</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/faqs/</guid>
      <description>Is Docker SSO available for all paid subscriptions? Docker single sign-on (SSO) is only available with the Docker Business subscription. Upgrade your existing subscription to start using Docker SSO.&#xA;How does Docker SSO work? Docker SSO lets users authenticate using their identity providers (IdPs) to access Docker. Docker supports Entra ID (formerly Azure AD) and any SAML 2.0 identity providers. When you enable SSO, this redirects users to your provider’s authentication page to authenticate using their email and password.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General security FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/general/</guid>
      <description>How do I report a vulnerability? If you’ve discovered a security vulnerability in Docker, we encourage you to report it responsibly. Report security issues to security@docker.com so that they can be quickly addressed by our team.&#xA;How are passwords managed when SSO isn&#39;t used? Passwords are encrypted and salt-hashed. If you use application-level passwords instead of SSO, you are responsible for ensuring that your employees know how to pick strong passwords, don&#39;t share passwords, and don&#39;t reuse passwords across multiple systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity providers</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/idp-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/idp-faqs/</guid>
      <description>Is it possible to use more than one IdP with Docker SSO? No. You can only configure Docker SSO to work with a single IdP. A domain can only be associated with a single IdP. Docker supports Entra ID (formerly Azure AD) and identity providers that support SAML 2.0.&#xA;Is it possible to change my identity provider after configuring SSO? Yes. You must delete your existing IdP configuration in your Docker SSO connection and then configure SSO using your new IdP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage users</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/users-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/single-sign-on/users-faqs/</guid>
      <description>How do I manage users when using SSO? You can manage users through organizations in Docker Hub or Admin Console. When you configure SSO in Docker, you need to make sure an account exists for each user in your IdP account. When a user signs in to Docker for the first time using their domain email address, they will be automatically added to the organization after a successful authentication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSI FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/desktop/install/msi/faq/</guid>
      <description>What happens to user data if they have an older Docker Desktop installation (i.e. .exe)? If they have an older .exe installation, users must uninstall this version before using the new MSI version. This deletes all Docker containers, images, volumes, and other Docker-related data local to the machine, and removes the files generated by the application. For older versions, users should backup any containers that they want to keep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network and VM FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/networking-and-vms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/faqs/networking-and-vms/</guid>
      <description>How can I limit the type of internet access allowed by the container when it runs, to prevent it from being able to exfiltrate data or download malicious code? There is no built-in mechanism for that but it can be addressed by process-level firewall on the host. Hook into the com.docker.vpnkit user-space process and apply rules where it can connect to (DNS URL white list; packet/payload filter) and which ports/protocols it is allowed to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subscription FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/subscription/faq/</guid>
      <description>For more information on Docker subscriptions, see Docker subscription overview.&#xA;Can I transfer my subscription from one user or organization account to another? Subscriptions are non-transferable.&#xA;Can I pause or delay my Docker subscription? You can&#39;t pause or delay a subscription, but you can downgrade. If a subscription invoice hasn&#39;t been paid on the due date, there&#39;s a 15 day grace period, including the due date.&#xA;Does Docker offer academic pricing?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
