<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker Build Cloud: Reclaim your time with fast, multi-architecture builds on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker Build Cloud: Reclaim your time with fast, multi-architecture builds on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Docker Build Cloud?</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/why/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Docker Build Cloud is a service that lets you build container images faster,&#xA;both locally and in CI. Builds run on cloud infrastructure optimally&#xA;dimensioned for your workloads, with no configuration required. The service&#xA;uses a remote build cache, ensuring fast builds anywhere and for all team&#xA;members.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Docker Build Cloud provides several benefits over local builds:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved build speed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shared build cache&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Native multi-platform builds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s no need to worry about managing builders or infrastructure — simply&#xA;connect to your builders and start building. Each cloud builder provisioned to&#xA;an organization is completely isolated to a single Amazon EC2 instance, with a&#xA;dedicated EBS volume for build cache and encryption in transit. That means&#xA;there are no shared processes or data between cloud builders.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demo: set up and use Docker Build Cloud in development</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/dev/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With Docker Build Cloud, you can easily shift the build workload from local machines&#xA;to the cloud, helping you achieve faster build times, especially for multi-platform builds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this demo, you&#39;ll see:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to setup the builder locally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to use Docker Build Cloud with Docker Compose&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How the image cache speeds up builds for others on your team&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div id=&#34;youtube-player-oPGq2AP5OtQ&#34; data-video-id=&#34;oPGq2AP5OtQ&#34; class=&#34;youtube-video aspect-video h-fit w-full py-2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div id=&#34;dbc-lp-survey-anchor&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demo: Using Docker Build Cloud in CI</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/ci/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Docker Build Cloud can significantly decrease the time it takes for your CI builds&#xA;take to run, saving you time and money.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since the builds run remotely, your CI runner can still use the Docker tooling CLI&#xA;without needing elevated permissions, making your builds more secure by default.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this demo, you will see:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to integrate Docker Build Cloud into a variety of CI platforms&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to use Docker Build Cloud in GitHub Actions to build multi-architecture images&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Speed differences between a workflow using Docker Build Cloud and a workflow running natively&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to use Docker Build Cloud in a GitLab Pipeline&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div id=&#34;youtube-player-wvLdInoVBGg&#34; data-video-id=&#34;wvLdInoVBGg&#34; class=&#34;youtube-video aspect-video h-fit w-full py-2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div id=&#34;dbc-lp-survey-anchor&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common challenges and questions</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/common-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/guides/docker-build-cloud/common-questions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 class=&#34; scroll-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;is-docker-build-cloud-a-standalone-product-or-a-part-of-docker-desktop&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;text-black dark:text-white no-underline hover:underline&#34; href=&#34;#is-docker-build-cloud-a-standalone-product-or-a-part-of-docker-desktop&#34;&gt;&#xA;    Is Docker Build Cloud a standalone product or a part of Docker Desktop?&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Docker Build Cloud is a service that can be used both with Docker Desktop and&#xA;standalone. It lets you build your container images faster, both locally and in&#xA;CI, with builds running on cloud infrastructure. The service uses a remote&#xA;build cache, ensuring fast builds anywhere and for all team members.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
