<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What is Enhanced Container Isolation? on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What is Enhanced Container Isolation? on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advanced configuration options</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/config/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;This feature is available with Docker Desktop version 4.27 (and later) on Mac, Linux, and Windows (Hyper-V). For Windows with WSL 2, this feature requires Docker Desktop 4.28 and later.&#xA;This page describes optional, advanced configurations for ECI, once ECI is enabled.&#xA;Docker socket mount permissions By default, when ECI is enabled, Docker Desktop does not allow bind-mounting the Docker Engine socket into containers:&#xA;$ docker run -it --rm -v /var/run/docker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Container Isolation (ECI) FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/faq/</guid>
      <description>Do I need to change the way I use Docker when ECI is switched on? No, you can continue to use Docker as usual. ECI works under the covers by creating a more secure container.&#xA;Do all container workloads work well with ECI? The great majority of container workloads run fine with ECI enabled, but a few do not (yet). For the few workloads that don&#39;t yet work with Enhanced Container Isolation, Docker is continuing to improve the feature to reduce this to a minimum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does it work?</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/how-eci-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/how-eci-works/</guid>
      <description>Docker implements Enhanced Container Isolation by using the Sysbox container runtime. Sysbox is a fork of the standard OCI runc runtime that was modified to enhance standard container isolation and workloads. For more details see Under the hood.&#xA;Starting with version 4.13, Docker Desktop includes a customized version of Sysbox.&#xA;When Enhanced Container Isolation is enabled, containers created by users through docker run or docker create are automatically launched using Sysbox instead of the standard OCI runc runtime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key features and benefits</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/features-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/features-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Linux User Namespace on all containers With Enhanced Container Isolation, all user containers leverage the Linux user-namespace for extra isolation. This means that the root user in the container maps to an unprivileged user in the Docker Desktop Linux VM.&#xA;For example:&#xA;$ docker run -it --rm --name=first alpine / # cat /proc/self/uid_map 0 100000 65536 The output 0 100000 65536 is the signature of the Linux user-namespace. It means that the root user (0) in the container is mapped to unprivileged user 100000 in the Docker Desktop Linux VM, and the mapping extends for a continuous range of 64K user IDs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limitations</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/limitations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/hardened-desktop/enhanced-container-isolation/limitations/</guid>
      <description>ECI support for WSL Prior to Docker Desktop 4.20, Enhanced Container Isolation (ECI) on Windows hosts was only supported when Docker Desktop was configured to use Hyper-V to create the Docker Desktop Linux VM. ECI was not supported when Docker Desktop was configured to use Windows Subsystem for Linux (aka WSL).&#xA;Starting with Docker Desktop 4.20, ECI is supported when Docker Desktop is configured to use either Hyper-V or WSL 2.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
