<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trusted content on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trusted content on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker Verified Publisher Program</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/dvp-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/dvp-program/</guid>
      <description>The Docker Verified Publisher Program provides high-quality images from commercial publishers verified by Docker.&#xA;These images help development teams build secure software supply chains, minimizing exposure to malicious content early in the process to save time and money later.&#xA;Images that are part of this program have a special badge on Docker Hub making it easier for users to identify projects that Docker has verified as high-quality commercial publishers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker-Sponsored Open Source Program</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/dsos-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/dsos-program/</guid>
      <description>Docker Sponsored Open Source images are published and maintained by open-source projects sponsored by Docker through the program.&#xA;Images that are part of this program have a special badge on Docker Hub making it easier for users to identify projects that Docker has verified as trusted, secure, and active open-source projects.&#xA;For content publishers The Docker-Sponsored Open Source (DSOS) Program provides several features and benefits to non-commercial open source developers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights and analytics</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/insights-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/trusted-content/insights-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Insights and analytics provides usage analytics for Docker Verified Publisher (DVP) and Docker-Sponsored Open Source (DSOS) images on Docker Hub. This includes self-serve access to image and extension usage metrics for a desired time span. You can also display the number of image pulls by tag or by digest, and get breakdowns by geolocation, cloud provider, client, and more.&#xA;Tip&#xA;Head to the Docker Verified Publisher Program or Docker-Sponsored Open Source pages to learn more about the programs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
