<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Set up Automated Builds on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Set up Automated Builds on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advanced options for Autobuild and Autotest</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/advanced/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Automated builds require a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;The following options allow you to customize your automated build and automated test processes.&#xA;Environment variables for building and testing Several utility environment variables are set by the build process, and are available during automated builds, automated tests, and while executing hooks.&#xA;Note&#xA;These environment variables are only available to the build and test processes and don&#39;t affect your service&#39;s run environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated repository tests</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/automated-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/automated-testing/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Automated builds require a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;Docker Hub can automatically test changes to your source code repositories using containers. You can enable Autotest on any Docker Hub repository to run tests on each pull request to the source code repository to create a continuous integration testing service.&#xA;Enabling Autotest builds an image for testing purposes, but does not automatically push the built image to the Docker repository.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure automated builds from GitHub and BitBucket</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/link-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/link-source/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Automated builds require a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;To automate building and testing of your images, you link to your hosted source code service to Docker Hub so that it can access your source code repositories. You can configure this link for user accounts or organizations.&#xA;If you are linking a source code provider to create autobuilds for a team, follow the instructions to create a service account for the team before linking the account as described below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Automated builds work</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/how-builds-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/how-builds-work/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Automated builds require a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;Docker Hub can automatically build images from source code in an external repository and automatically push the built image to your Docker repositories.&#xA;When you set up Automated builds, also called autobuilds, you create a list of branches and tags that you want to build into Docker images. When you push code to a source-code branch, for example in GitHub, for one of those listed image tags, the push uses a webhook to trigger a new build, which produces a Docker image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage autobuilds</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/manage-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/manage-builds/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Automated builds require a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;Cancel or retry a build While a build is in queue or running, a Cancel icon appears next to its build report link on the General tab and on the Builds tab. You can also select Cancel on the Build report page, or from the Timeline tab&#39;s logs display for the build.&#xA;Check your active builds A summary of a repository&#39;s builds appears both on the repository General tab, and in the Builds tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot your autobuilds</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/troubleshoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/docker-hub/builds/troubleshoot/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Automated builds require a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;Failing builds If a build fails, a Retry icon appears next to the build report line on the General and Builds tabs. The Build report page and Timeline logs also display a Retry button.&#xA;Note&#xA;If you are viewing the build details for a repository that belongs to an organization, the Cancel and Retry buttons only appear if you have Read &amp;amp; Write access to the repository.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
