<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview of installing Docker Compose on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview of installing Docker Compose on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Compose standalone</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/standalone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/standalone/</guid>
      <description>On this page you can find instructions on how to install Compose standalone on Linux or Windows Server, from the command line.&#xA;On Linux Compose standalone&#xA;Note that Compose standalone uses the -compose syntax instead of the current standard syntax compose.&#xA;For example type docker-compose up when using Compose standalone, instead of docker compose up.&#xA;To download and install Compose standalone, run:&#xA;$ curl -SL https://github.com/docker/compose/releases/download/v2.28.1/docker-compose-linux-x86_64 -o /usr/local/bin/docker-compose Apply executable permissions to the standalone binary in the target path for the installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Compose plugin</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/linux/</guid>
      <description>On this page you can find instructions on how to install the Compose plugin on Linux from the command line.&#xA;To install the Compose plugin on Linux, you can either:&#xA;Set up Docker&#39;s repository on your Linux system. Install Compose manually. Note&#xA;These instructions assume you already have Docker Engine and Docker CLI installed and now want to install the Compose plugin.&#xA;For Compose standalone, see Install Compose Standalone.&#xA;Install using the repository Set up the repository.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall Docker Compose</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/uninstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/compose/install/uninstall/</guid>
      <description>Uninstalling Docker Compose depends on the method you have used to install Docker Compose. On this page you can find specific instructions to uninstall Docker Compose.&#xA;Uninstalling Docker Desktop If you want to uninstall Compose and you have installed Docker Desktop, see Uninstall Docker Desktop.&#xA;Note&#xA;Unless you have other Docker instances installed on that specific environment, you would be removing Docker altogether by uninstalling the Desktop.&#xA;Uninstalling the Docker Compose CLI plugin To remove the Compose CLI plugin, run:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
