<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enable two-factor authentication for Docker Hub on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enable two-factor authentication for Docker Hub on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Disable two-factor authentication on Docker Hub</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/disable-2fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/disable-2fa/</guid>
      <description>Warning&#xA;Disabling two-factor authentication results in decreased security for your Docker Hub account.&#xA;Sign in to your Docker Hub account. Select your avatar and then from the drop-down menu, select Account settings. Navigate to the Security tab and select Manage Two-Factor Authentication. Enter your password, then select Confirm. Select Disable 2FA. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate a new recovery code</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/new-recovery-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/new-recovery-code/</guid>
      <description>If you have lost your two-factor authentication recovery code and still have access to your Docker Hub account, you can generate a new recovery code.&#xA;Sign in to your Docker Hub account. Select your avatar and then from the drop-down menu, select Account settings. Navigate to the Security tab and select Manage Two-Factor Authentication. Enter your password, then select Confirm. In the Manage recovery code section, you can view your recovery code or generate a new code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recover your Docker account</title>
      <link>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/recover-hub-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docker.qubitpi.org/security/for-developers/2fa/recover-hub-account/</guid>
      <description>If you have lost access to both your two-factor authentication application and your recovery code:&#xA;Navigate to Docker Hub and enter your username and password. Select I&#39;ve lost my authentication device and I&#39;ve lost my recovery code. Complete the Contact Support form. You must enter the primary email address associated with your Docker ID in the Contact Support form for recovery instructions. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
