<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview of Docker Desktop on Docker Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview of Docker Desktop on Docker Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.docker.com/desktop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Allowlist for Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/allow-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/allow-list/</guid>
      <description>This page contains the domain URLs that you need to add to a firewall allowlist to ensure Docker Desktop works properly within your organization.&#xA;Domain URLs to allow Domains Description https://api.segment.io Analytics https://cdn.segment.com Analytics https://api.wootric.com Analytics https://cdn.wootric.com Analytics https://notify.bugsnag.com Error reports https://sessions.bugsnag.com Error reports https://auth.docker.io Authentication https://cdn.auth0.com Authentication https://login.docker.com Authentication https://desktop.docker.com Update https://hub.docker.com Docker Pull/Push https://registry-1.docker.io Docker Pull/Push https://production.cloudflare.docker.com Docker Pull/Push https://docker-pinata-support.s3.amazonaws.com Troubleshooting https://api.dso.docker.com Docker Scout service </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Docker Desktop settings on Linux</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/settings/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/settings/linux/</guid>
      <description>This page provides information on how to configure and manage your Docker Desktop settings.&#xA;To navigate to Settings either:&#xA;Select the Docker menu and then Settings Select the Settings icon from the Docker Dashboard. You can also locate the settings.json file at ~/.docker/desktop/settings.json.&#xA;General On the General tab, you can configure when to start Docker and specify other settings:&#xA;Start Docker Desktop when you sign in to your computer. Select to automatically start Docker Desktop when you sign in to your machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Docker Desktop settings on Mac</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/settings/mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/settings/mac/</guid>
      <description>This page provides information on how to configure and manage your Docker Desktop for Mac settings.&#xA;To navigate to Settings either:&#xA;Select the Docker menu and then Settings Select the Settings icon from the Docker Dashboard. You can also locate the settings.json file at ~/Library/Group Containers/group.com.docker/settings.json.&#xA;General On the General tab, you can configure when to start Docker and specify other settings:&#xA;Start Docker Desktop when you sign in to your computer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Docker Desktop settings on Windows</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/settings/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/settings/windows/</guid>
      <description>This page provides information on how to configure and manage your Docker Desktop settings.&#xA;To navigate to Settings either:&#xA;Select the Docker menu and then Settings Select the Settings icon from the Docker Dashboard. You can also locate the settings.json file at C:\Users\[USERNAME]\AppData\Roaming\Docker\settings.json.&#xA;General On the General tab, you can configure when to start Docker and specify other settings:&#xA;Start Docker Desktop when you sign in to your computer. Select to automatically start Docker Desktop when you sign in to your machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>containerd image store</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/containerd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/containerd/</guid>
      <description>This page provides information about the ongoing integration of containerd for image and file system management in the Docker Engine.&#xA;Note&#xA;After switching to the containerd image store, images and containers in the classic image store won&#39;t be visible. All of those containers and images still exist. To see them again, turn off the containerd image store feature.&#xA;What is containerd? containerd is an abstraction of the low-level kernel features used to run and manage containers on a system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy on Kubernetes with Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop includes a standalone Kubernetes server and client, as well as Docker CLI integration that runs on your machine.&#xA;The Kubernetes server runs locally within your Docker instance, is not configurable, and is a single-node cluster. It runs within a Docker container on your local system, and is only for local testing.&#xA;Turning on Kubernetes allows you to deploy your workloads in parallel, on Kubernetes, Swarm, and as standalone containers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop for Mac 2.x release notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/2.x-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/2.x-mac/</guid>
      <description>This page contains release notes for Docker Desktop for Mac 2.x.&#xA;Docker Desktop Community 2.5.0.1 2020-11-10&#xA;Upgrades Compose CLI v1.0.2 Snyk v1.424.4 Bug fixes and minor changes Fixed an issue that caused Docker Desktop to crash on MacOS 11.0 (Big Sur) when VirtualBox was also installed. See docker/for-mac#4997. Docker Desktop Community 2.5.0.0 2020-11-02&#xA;Docker Desktop 2.5.0.0 contains a Kubernetes upgrade. Your local Kubernetes cluster will be reset after installing this version.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop for Mac 3.x release notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/3.x-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/3.x-mac/</guid>
      <description>This page contains release notes for Docker Desktop for Mac 3.x.&#xA;Docker Desktop 3.6.0 2021-08-11&#xA;New Dev Environments: You can now create a Dev Environment from your local Git repository. Volume Management: You can now sort volumes by the name, the date created, and the size of the volume. You can also search for specific volumes using the Search field. For more information, see Explore volumes. Upgrades Compose V2 RC1 Docker compose command line completion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop for Mac Edge release notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/edge-releases-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/edge-releases-mac/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about Docker Desktop Edge releases. Edge releases give you early access to our newest features. Note that some of the features may be experimental, and some of them may not ever reach the Stable release.&#xA;For Docker Desktop system requirements, see What to know before you install.&#xA;Docker Desktop Community 2.5.4 2020-12-07&#xA;Upgrades Docker Engine 20.10.0-rc2 Go 1.15.6 Bug fixes and minor changes Changed the «Update and quit» menu entry to «Update and restart».</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop for Windows Edge Release notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/edge-releases-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/edge-releases-windows/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about Docker Desktop Edge releases. Edge releases give you early access to our newest features. Note that some of the features may be experimental, and some of them may not ever reach the Stable release.&#xA;For Docker Desktop system requirements, see What to know before you install.&#xA;Docker Desktop Community 2.5.4 2020-12-07&#xA;Upgrades Docker Engine 20.10.0-rc2 Go 1.15.6 Bug fixes and minor changes Fixed an issue causing the background update to fail when the current user is not an administrator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop release notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the new features, improvements, known issues, and bug fixes in Docker Desktop releases. For frequently asked questions about Docker Desktop releases, see FAQs.&#xA;Docker Desktop versions older than 6 months from the latest release are not available for download.&#xA;Take a look at the Docker Public Roadmap to see what&#39;s coming next.&#xA;4.32.0 2024-07-04 Download Docker Desktop&#xA;Windows (checksum) | Windows ARM Beta (checksum) | Mac with Apple chip (checksum) | Mac with Intel chip (checksum) | Debian - RPM - Arch (checksum)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker for Windows 2.x release notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/2.x-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/2.x-windows/</guid>
      <description>This page contains release notes for Docker Desktop for Windows 2.x.&#xA;Docker Desktop Community 2.5.0.1 2020-11-10&#xA;Upgrades Compose CLI v1.0.2 Snyk v1.424.4 Docker Desktop Community 2.5.0.0 2020-11-02&#xA;Docker Desktop 2.5.0.0 contains a Kubernetes upgrade. Your local Kubernetes cluster will be reset after installing this version.&#xA;New Users with a paid Docker subscription can now see the vulnerability scan report on the Remote repositories tab in Docker Desktop. Docker Desktop introduces a support option for users who have a paid Docker subscription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker for Windows 3.x release notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/3.x-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/3.x-windows/</guid>
      <description>This page contains release notes for Docker Desktop for Windows 3.x.&#xA;Docker Desktop 3.6.0 2021-08-11&#xA;New Dev Environments: You can now create a Dev Environment from your local Git repository. Volume Management: You can now sort volumes by the name, the date created, and the size of the volume. You can also search for specific volumes using the Search field. For more information, see Explore volumes. Upgrades Compose V2 RC1 Docker compose command line completion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore networking features on Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/networking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/networking/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop provides several networking features to make it easier to use.&#xA;Networking features for all platforms VPN Passthrough Docker Desktop networking can work when attached to a VPN. To do this, Docker Desktop intercepts traffic from the containers and injects it into the host as if it originated from the Docker application.&#xA;Port mapping When you run a container with the -p argument, for example:&#xA;$ docker run -p 80:80 -d nginx Docker Desktop makes whatever is running on port 80 in the container, in this case, nginx, available on port 80 of localhost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs for Docker Desktop for Linux</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/linuxfaqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/linuxfaqs/</guid>
      <description>Why does Docker Desktop for Linux run a VM? Docker Desktop for Linux runs a Virtual Machine (VM) for the following reasons:&#xA;To ensure that Docker Desktop provides a consistent experience across platforms.&#xA;During research, the most frequently cited reason for users wanting Docker Desktop for Linux was to ensure a consistent Docker Desktop experience with feature parity across all major operating systems. Utilizing a VM ensures that the Docker Desktop experience for Linux users will closely match that of Windows and macOS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs for Docker Desktop for Mac</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/macfaqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/macfaqs/</guid>
      <description>What is HyperKit? HyperKit is a hypervisor built on top of the Hypervisor.framework in macOS. It runs entirely in userspace and has no other dependencies.&#xA;We use HyperKit to eliminate the need for other VM products, such as Oracle VirtualBox or VMWare Fusion.&#xA;What is the benefit of HyperKit? HyperKit is thinner than VirtualBox and VMWare fusion, and the version included is customized for Docker workloads on Mac.&#xA;Why is com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs for Docker Desktop for Windows</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/windowsfaqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/windowsfaqs/</guid>
      <description>Can I use VirtualBox alongside Docker Desktop? Yes, you can run VirtualBox along with Docker Desktop if you have enabled the Windows Hypervisor Platform feature on your machine.&#xA;Why is Windows 10 or Windows 11 required? Docker Desktop uses the Windows Hyper-V features. While older Windows versions have Hyper-V, their Hyper-V implementations lack features critical for Docker Desktop to work.&#xA;Can I run Docker Desktop on Windows Server? No, running Docker Desktop on Windows Server is not supported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs on Docker Desktop releases</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/releases/</guid>
      <description>How frequent will new releases be? New releases are available roughly every month, unless there are critical fixes that need to be released sooner.&#xA;The Automatically check for updates setting in the Software updates tab is turned on by default. This means you receive notifications in the Docker menu and a notification badge on the Docker Dashboard when a new version is available.&#xA;You can also let Docker Desktop automatically download new updates in the background by selecting the Always download updates checkbox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General FAQs for Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/faqs/general/</guid>
      <description>Can I use Docker Desktop offline? Yes, you can use Docker Desktop offline. However, you cannot access features that require an active internet connection. Additionally, any functionality that requires you to sign in won&#39;t work while using Docker Desktop offline or in air-gapped environments. This includes:&#xA;The resources in the Learning Center Pulling or pushing an image to Docker Hub Image Access Management Static vulnerability scanning Viewing remote images in the Docker Dashboard Setting up Dev Environments Docker Build when using BuildKit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get support</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/support/</guid>
      <description>Find information on how to get support, and the scope of Docker Desktop support.&#xA;Docker Desktop offers support for developers subscribed to a Pro, Team, or a Business tier. Upgrade now to benefit from Docker Support.&#xA;Upgrade now How do I get Docker Desktop support? If you have a paid Docker subscription, raise a ticket through Docker Desktop support.&#xA;Docker Community users can get support through our Github repos for-win, for-mac, for-linux, where we respond on a best-effort basis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give feedback</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/feedback/</guid>
      <description>There are many ways you can provide feedback on Docker Desktop or Docker Desktop features.&#xA;In-product feedback On each Docker Dashboard view, there is a Give feedback link. This sends you to a Google feedback form where you can share your feedback and ideas.&#xA;You can also use the docker feedback command to submit feedback directly from the command line.&#xA;Feedback via Docker Community forums To get help from the community, review current user topics, join or start a discussion, sign in to the appropriate Docker forums:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPU support in Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/gpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/gpu/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Currently GPU support in Docker Desktop is only available on Windows with the WSL2 backend.&#xA;Using NVIDIA GPUs with WSL2 Docker Desktop for Windows supports WSL 2 GPU Paravirtualization (GPU-PV) on NVIDIA GPUs. To enable WSL 2 GPU Paravirtualization, you need:&#xA;A machine with an NVIDIA GPU Up to date Windows 10 or Windows 11 installation Up to date drivers from NVIDIA supporting WSL 2 GPU Paravirtualization The latest version of the WSL 2 Linux kernel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to back up and restore your Docker Desktop data</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/backup-and-restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/backup-and-restore/</guid>
      <description>Use the following procedure to save and restore your images and container data. This is useful if you want to reset your VM disk or to move your Docker environment to a new computer, for example.&#xA;Should I back up my containers?&#xA;If you use volumes or bind-mounts to store your container data, backing up your containers may not be needed, but make sure to remember the options that were used when creating the container or use a Docker Compose file if you want to re-create your containers with the same configuration after re-installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on Arch-based distributions</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/archlinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/archlinux/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This topic discusses installation of Docker Desktop from an Arch package that Docker provides in addition to the supported platforms. Docker has not tested or verified the installation.&#xA;Arch package (experimental) For checksums, see Release notes&#xA;Prerequisites To install Docker Desktop successfully, you must meet the system requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on Debian</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/debian/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This page contains information on how to install, launch, and upgrade Docker Desktop on a Debian distribution.&#xA;DEB package For checksums, see Release notes&#xA;Prerequisites To install Docker Desktop successfully, you must:&#xA;Meet the system requirements.&#xA;Have a 64-bit version of Debian 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on Fedora</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/fedora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/fedora/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This page contains information on how to install, launch and upgrade Docker Desktop on a Fedora distribution.&#xA;RPM package Prerequisites To install Docker Desktop successfully, you must:&#xA;Meet the system requirements. Have a 64-bit version of Fedora 39 or Fedora 40. Additionally, for a GNOME desktop environment you must install AppIndicator and KStatusNotifierItem GNOME extensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on Linux</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/linux-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/linux-install/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This page contains information about general system requirements, supported platforms, and instructions on how to install Docker Desktop for Linux.&#xA;Important&#xA;Docker Desktop on Linux runs a Virtual Machine (VM) which creates and uses a custom docker context, desktop-linux, on startup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on Mac</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/mac-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/mac-install/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This page contains download URLs, information about system requirements, and instructions on how to install Docker Desktop for Mac.&#xA;Docker Desktop for Mac with Apple silicon Docker Desktop for Mac with Intel chip For checksums, see Release notes.&#xA;System requirements Mac with Intel chip Mac with Apple silicon A supported version of macOS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on RHEL</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/rhel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/rhel/</guid>
      <description>Early Access&#xA;Docker Desktop on RHEL is in Early Access.&#xA;Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This page contains information on how to install, launch and upgrade Docker Desktop on a Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) distribution.&#xA;Prerequisites To install Docker Desktop successfully, you must:&#xA;Meet the system requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This page contains information on how to install, launch and upgrade Docker Desktop on an Ubuntu distribution.&#xA;DEB package For checksums, see Release notes&#xA;Prerequisites To install Docker Desktop successfully, you must:&#xA;Meet the system requirements&#xA;Have a 64-bit version of either the LTS version Ubuntu Jammy Jellyfish 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker Desktop on Windows</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/windows-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/install/windows-install/</guid>
      <description>Docker Desktop terms&#xA;Commercial use of Docker Desktop in larger enterprises (more than 250 employees OR more than $10 million USD in annual revenue) requires a paid subscription.&#xA;This page contains the download URL, information about system requirements, and instructions on how to install Docker Desktop for Windows.&#xA;Docker Desktop for Windows - x86_64 Docker Desktop for Windows - Arm (Beta) For checksums, see Release notes&#xA;System requirements WSL 2 backend, x86_64 Hyper-V backend, x86_64 WSL 2 backend, Arm (Beta) WSL version 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known issues</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/known-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/known-issues/</guid>
      <description>For all platforms For Mac with Intel chip For Mac with Apple silicon IPv6 is not yet supported on Docker Desktop. The Mac Activity Monitor reports that Docker is using twice the amount of memory it&#39;s actually using. This is due to a bug in MacOS. We have written a detailed report on this.&#xA;Force-ejecting the .dmg after running Docker.app from it can cause the whale icon to become unresponsive, Docker tasks to show as not responding in the Activity Monitor, and for some processes to consume a large amount of CPU resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes for previous versions</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/archive-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/archive-mac/</guid>
      <description>This page contains release notes for older versions of Docker Desktop for Mac.&#xA;Stable Releases of 2018 Docker Community Edition 18.06.1-ce-mac73 2018-08-29 Upgrades&#xA;Docker 18.06.1-ce Bug fixes and minor changes&#xA;Fix local DNS failing to resolve inside containers. Docker Community Edition 18.06.0-ce-mac70 2018-07-25 Upgrades&#xA;Docker 18.06.0-ce Docker Machine 0.15.0 Docker compose 1.22.0 LinuxKit v0.5 Linux Kernel 4.9.93 with CEPH, DRBD, RBD, MPLS_ROUTING and MPLS_IPTUNNEL enabled New&#xA;Kubernetes Support. You can now run a single-node Kubernetes cluster from the &amp;quot;Kubernetes&amp;quot; Pane in Docker For Mac Preferences and use kubectl commands as well as docker commands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes for previous versions</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/archive-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/previous-versions/archive-windows/</guid>
      <description>This page contains release notes for older versions of Docker Desktop for Windows.&#xA;Stable Releases of 2018 Docker Community Edition 18.06.1-ce-win73 2018-08-29 Upgrades&#xA;Docker 18.06.1-ce Bug fixes and minor changes&#xA;Fix bug in VM activity detection, preventing Docker Desktop from starting. Fixes docker/for-win#2404 Fix bug in detection when Windows service is not running, and propose to restart the service. Fix local DNS failing to resolve inside containers. Fixes docker/for-win#2301, docker/for-win#2304 Fix Kubernetes status display after reset to factory default Fix bug where host.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run Docker Desktop for Windows in a VM or VDI environment</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/vm-vdi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/vm-vdi/</guid>
      <description>In general, we recommend running Docker Desktop natively on either Mac, Linux, or Windows. However, Docker Desktop for Windows can run inside a virtual desktop provided the virtual desktop is properly configured.&#xA;To run Docker Desktop in a virtual desktop environment, it is essential nested virtualization is enabled on the virtual machine that provides the virtual desktop. This is because, under the hood, Docker Desktop is using a Linux VM in which it runs Docker Engine and the containers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign in to Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/get-started/</guid>
      <description>Docker recommends that you authenticate using the Sign in option in the top-right corner of the Docker Dashboard.&#xA;In large enterprises where admin access is restricted, administrators can enforce sign-in.&#xA;Tip&#xA;Explore Docker&#39;s core subscriptions to see what else Docker can offer you.&#xA;Benefits of signing in You can access your Docker Hub repositories directly from Docker Desktop.&#xA;Authenticated users also get a higher pull rate limit compared to anonymous users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synchronized file shares</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/synchronized-file-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/synchronized-file-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Note&#xA;Synchronized file shares is available with Docker Desktop version 4.27 and later. It is available for customers with a Docker Pro, Team, or Business subscription.&#xA;Synchronized file shares is an alternative file sharing mechanism that provides fast and flexible host-to-VM file sharing, enhancing bind mount performance through the use of synchronized filesystem caches.&#xA;Who is it for? Synchronized file shares is ideal for developers who:&#xA;Have large repositories or monorepos with 100 000 files or more totaling hundreds of megabytes or even gigabytes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/overview/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information on how to diagnose and troubleshoot Docker Desktop, and how to check the logs.&#xA;Troubleshoot menu To navigate to Troubleshoot either:&#xA;Select the Docker menu and then Troubleshoot Select the Troubleshoot icon near the top-right corner of Docker Dashboard The Troubleshoot page contains the following options:&#xA;Restart Docker Desktop.&#xA;Get support. Users with a paid Docker subscription can use this option to send a support request. Other users can use this option to diagnose any issues in Docker Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot topics for Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/topics/</guid>
      <description>Tip&#xA;If you do not find a solution in troubleshooting, browse the GitHub repositories or create a new issue:&#xA;docker/for-mac docker/for-win docker/for-linux Topics for all platforms Make sure certificates are set up correctly Docker Desktop ignores certificates listed under insecure registries, and does not send client certificates to them. Commands like docker run that attempt to pull from the registry produces error messages on the command line, like this:&#xA;Error response from daemon: Get http://192.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand permission requirements for Docker Desktop on Mac</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/mac/permission-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/mac/permission-requirements/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the permission requirements for running and installing Docker Desktop on Mac.&#xA;It also provides clarity on running containers as root as opposed to having root access on the host.&#xA;Permission requirements Docker Desktop for Mac is run as an unprivileged user. However, Docker Desktop requires certain functionalities to perform a limited set of privileged configurations such as:&#xA;Installing symlinks in/usr/local/bin. Binding privileged ports that are less than 1024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand permission requirements for Windows</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/windows/permission-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/windows/permission-requirements/</guid>
      <description>This page contains information about the permission requirements for running and installing Docker Desktop on Windows, the functionality of the privileged helper process com.docker.service and the reasoning behind this approach.&#xA;It also provides clarity on running containers as root as opposed to having Administrator access on the host and the privileges of the Windows Docker engine and Windows containers.&#xA;Permission requirements While Docker Desktop on Windows can be run without having Administrator privileges, it does require them during installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall Docker Desktop</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/uninstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/uninstall/</guid>
      <description>Warning&#xA;Uninstalling Docker Desktop destroys Docker containers, images, volumes, and other Docker-related data local to the machine, and removes the files generated by the application. To learn how to preserve important data before uninstalling, refer to the back up and restore data section .&#xA;Windows Mac Linux Ubuntu Debian Fedora Arch To uninstall Docker Desktop from your Windows machine:&#xA;From the Windows Start menu, select Settings &amp;gt; Apps &amp;gt; Apps &amp;amp; features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasm workloads (Beta)</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/wasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/wasm/</guid>
      <description>Beta&#xA;The Wasm feature is currently in Beta. We recommend that you do not use this feature in production environments as this feature may change or be removed from future releases.&#xA;Wasm (short for WebAssembly) is a fast, light alternative to the Linux and Windows containers you’re using in Docker today (with some tradeoffs).&#xA;This page provides information about the new ability to run Wasm applications alongside your Linux containers in Docker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workarounds for common problems</title>
      <link>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/workarounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.docker.com/desktop/troubleshoot/workarounds/</guid>
      <description>Reboot Restart your PC to stop / discard any vestige of the daemon running from the previously installed version.&#xA;Unset DOCKER_HOST The DOCKER_HOST environmental variable does not need to be set. If you use bash, use the command unset ${!DOCKER_*} to unset it. For other shells, consult the shell&#39;s documentation.&#xA;Make sure Docker is running for webserver examples For the hello-world-nginx example and others, Docker Desktop must be running to get to the webserver on http://localhost/.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
